好吧，现在是12:30，所以让我给您一些其他提醒
all right it's 12:30 so let me give you some reminders for the rest of the
some reminders for the rest of the semester the presentations for the class
学期的课程介绍，这意味着报告六页
semester the presentations for the class which means the report the six pages
which means the report the six pages report the PowerPoint slides you're all
报告所有您都只是演示文稿的PowerPoint幻灯片，这将是最后一个
report the PowerPoint slides you're all a presentation are going to be the last
a presentation are going to be the last three lectures in April okay because
四月份的三个讲座还可以，因为从过去的经验来看，没有
three lectures in April okay because there's from past experience there's no
there's from past experience there's no way we can find another room in May so
我们可以在五月找到另一个房间的方式，所以他们会在最后一个
way we can find another room in May so they're going to be during the last
they're going to be during the last week's which means plan ahead right
一周，这意味着正确的计划不会停下来，说我可以成为最后一个
week's which means plan ahead right don't stop and say can I be the last
don't stop and say can I be the last because you are being called and you
因为你被叫了，你会是第一个没事的，它不会走
because you are being called and you will be the first okay and it doesn't go
will be the first okay and it doesn't go first come first serve on this case lost
先到先得，在这种情况下先浪费自己的时间，但是您可以抛光一下吗
first come first serve on this case lost time to itself but can you polish which
time to itself but can you polish which means five down here from you your first
意思是说，从你这里下来有五个你的第一件事，那就是第二件事
means five down here from you your first okay that's one thing the second thing
okay that's one thing the second thing is ie you know we were planning to give
就是说，您知道我们正计划给您六份作业，并在那里待得很久。
is ie you know we were planning to give you six homeworks and staying there very
you six homeworks and staying there very slow process of even preparing the
准备作业解决方案的过程很慢
slow process of even preparing the solutions of the homeworks
solutions of the homeworks you know I asked stovic to give you a
你知道我要斯托维奇给你六份功课，还给你
you know I asked stovic to give you a six homework but also to give you the
six homework but also to give you the solution so you can study them but we
解决方案，以便您可以研究它们，但我们不必提交六种激素就可以了
solution so you can study them but we won't have to submit at six hormone okay
won't have to submit at six hormone okay I'm not doing this to reward anybody I
我不是为了奖励我意识到事情进展不顺利的任何人
I'm not doing this to reward anybody I realized things are not going as the way
realized things are not going as the way I envisioned so I think that's the best
我设想到了，所以我认为这是每个人的最佳选择，那又如何呢？
I envisioned so I think that's the best option for everybody all right so what
option for everybody all right so what else
否则谢谢你帮我忘了好吧
else thank you helps I forgot all right so
thank you helps I forgot all right so what I'm going to do is because we went
我要做的是因为我们实际上花了八分钟来讲
what I'm going to do is because we went over literally eight minutes to cover
over literally eight minutes to cover variational inference for linear
线性回归的变分推论今天我要回去
variational inference for linear regression I'm going to go back today
regression I'm going to go back today and spend maybe fifteen minutes on the
并花15分钟在主题上，好吧，从某种意义上说，如果您
and spend maybe fifteen minutes on the topic okay and in some sense if you're
topic okay and in some sense if you're not talking about linear regression
不是在谈论线性回归，而是在
not talking about linear regression seeing this in the context of
seeing this in the context of variational algorithms is good because
变分算法很好，因为结果变化很大，它们看起来非常接近
variational algorithms is good because the results vary they look very close to
the results vary they look very close to the exact inference that you can do for
可以针对此类问题进行准确的推断，然后
the exact inference that you can do for this type of problem all right and then
this type of problem all right and then once we're finished with us we will
一旦完成，我们将讨论高斯混合
once we're finished with us we will discuss about the Gaussian mixture
discuss about the Gaussian mixture problem which is mathematically very
这个问题在数学上非常密集，但也更有用
problem which is mathematically very more intensive but also way more useful
more intensive but also way more useful and then maybe we'll generalize this to
然后也许我们将其概括为来自
and then maybe we'll generalize this to sort of any distributions from the
sort of any distributions from the exponential community and next Tuesday
指数社区，下周二我们将开始讨论近似值
exponential community and next Tuesday we start talking about approximate
we start talking about approximate methods interest methods in graphs in
图中的方法特别是期望传播中的方法
methods interest methods in graphs in particularly expectation propagation
particularly expectation propagation which is sort of one of the standard
这是在很长的时间内进行推理的标准方法之一
which is sort of one of the standard methods for doing inference in very
methods for doing inference in very complex systems things will get
复杂的系统，事情会变得越来越复杂，好了，你
complex systems things will get progressively more complex okay and you
progressively more complex okay and you may say but this is but this fixes is
可能会说，但这是但此修复程序不是机器学习的，不是机器
may say but this is but this fixes is not machine learning no it is machine
not machine learning no it is machine learning it's not statistics it's not
了解这不是统计信息，不是决策，对此了解不多
learning it's not statistics it's not decisions don't know much about this
decisions don't know much about this machine learning people need to know
机器学习的人需要知道更多，所以我说这是为了避免
machine learning people need to know more okay so I'm saying this to avoid
more okay so I'm saying this to avoid any comments questions probation
任何评论问题缓刑回归，所以我们基本上得到X
any comments questions probation regression so we basically were given X
regression so we basically were given X Y data if you like pairs of data the Y
Y数据（如果您喜欢数据对），此处的Y用T表示，所以我正在使用I
Y data if you like pairs of data the Y here is denoted with T so I'm using I
here is denoted with T so I'm using I think the notation is must be from this
认为符号必须来自此报告的猜测，因此集成
think the notation is must be from this report guessing so the integration comes
report guessing so the integration comes we write a response t
我们写了一个回应t NEX P没有美丽的过程P
we write a response t NEX there's no beautimous course P for P
NEX there's no beautimous course P for P is a vector basis functions you can
是向量基函数，您可以认为这是一维的
is a vector basis functions you can think of this being in one dimension for
think of this being in one dimension for example 1 xx square can be splines can
示例1 xx平方可以是样条曲线可以是正则函数可以
example 1 xx square can be splines can be regular basis functions can be
be regular basis functions can be anything okay and one side some noise
一切正常，并且一侧有些杂音，如果您以概率写出
anything okay and one side some noise and if you write this in a probabilistic
and if you write this in a probabilistic form the likelihood for iid data looks
形成iid数据的可能性看起来就可以了，所以现在让
form the likelihood for iid data looks like that okay so now to make the
like that okay so now to make the analysis simple here I'm going to take
分析简单，这里我将采用此模型中的精度为null且
analysis simple here I'm going to take the precision in this model is null and
the precision in this model is null and I think they have two or three slides in
我认为他们的笔记中有两张或三张幻灯片，基本上我们可以删除这些幻灯片
I think they have two or three slides in the notes where basically we can remove
the notes where basically we can remove that constrain and it doesn't have
这样的约束，对它来说并没有太大的困难
that constrain and it doesn't have really any much difficulty to the
really any much difficulty to the problem so in this integration right the
问题，所以在这种集成中，想法是我们将承担一切
problem so in this integration right the idea is we're going to take everything
idea is we're going to take everything to be random so W is going to come with
是随机的，所以W会带有一些先验分布和先验分布
to be random so W is going to come with some prior distribution and the prior
some prior distribution and the prior defense of this precision alpha and you
精确的alpha防御，您知道我们将承担所有
defense of this precision alpha and you know we're going to assume and all the
know we're going to assume and all the hyper prior basically pure alpha the
超级先验基本上是纯alpha伽马分布，您应该知道
hyper prior basically pure alpha the gamma distribution you should know that
gamma distribution you should know that gamma distribution comes all which is a
伽马分布是所有这些的先决条件，您可以知道每个查询的精度
gamma distribution comes all which is a prior for precision you know every query
prior for precision you know every query much similar okay and I think we also
非常相似，我想我们也讨论了可以对此进行概括的内容
much similar okay and I think we also discussed what you can generalize this
discussed what you can generalize this where you make the softest not to be
在最柔和的地方，不要让我减去Alpha，但我可以放一个
where you make the softest not to be alpha minus one I but you can put a
alpha minus one I but you can put a different alpha in the diagonal of the
协方差对角线中的不同alpha值，这就是您得到此结果的方式
different alpha in the diagonal of the covariance and that's how you get this
covariance and that's how you get this relevance determination methods you can
相关性确定方法，您可以找出需要使用哪个WS
relevance determination methods you can figure out which of the WS are needed to
figure out which of the WS are needed to to do the proper digression but right
做适当的题外话，但是现在这就是我们所能做的
to do the proper digression but right now this is what we have okay
now this is what we have okay we've seen the traditional unethical
我们已经看到了传统的不道德解决方案，您不会想到这个问题
we've seen the traditional unethical solution this problem you don't suppose
solution this problem you don't suppose to know if you know nothing about the
要知道您是否对回归一无所知，我们将尝试从
to know if you know nothing about the regression we will try to do this from
regression we will try to do this from scratch in the context of variational
在变分推理的上下文中从头开始，所以对变分
scratch in the context of variational inference so to the variational
inference so to the variational inference we need to join like liquid
推论我们需要像液体一样加入，这是我的方程W是一个alpha
inference we need to join like liquid and here is my equations W an alpha
and here is my equations W an alpha parameters so the drawing likelihood
参数，所以绘图的可能性这笔写的P给定了，你写出来就好了
parameters so the drawing likelihood this written P given lovely you write it
this written P given lovely you write it doesn't depend anything but W there is a
不依赖任何东西，但是W有一点点，但是我要变得更大
doesn't depend anything but W there is a bit of there but I'm taking bigger to be
bit of there but I'm taking bigger to be constant you have that we give an
常量，您可以给我们替换视图爸爸还可以，基本上
constant you have that we give an alternate view Papa okay and basically
alternate view Papa okay and basically this is sort of since we talked about
这是因为我们讨论的是基本发布图形模型
this is sort of since we talked about published the graphical models basically
published the graphical models basically would have found a picture like this
本来会找到这样的图片，这没有什么大问题
would have found a picture like this this defines no big questions we have
this defines no big questions we have seen up to now okay so we're going
到现在为止都可以看到，所以我们要去普雷斯顿，要做所有的参数
seen up to now okay so we're going Preston we want to do all the parameters
Preston we want to do all the parameters here of W and alpha so we won't
W和alpha在这里，所以我们不会近似W naught的后验
here of W and alpha so we won't approximate the posterior of W naught
approximate the posterior of W naught forgiven t and since we're star
原谅了，因为我们是明星推论，所以布鲁克斯的范围真的很像
forgiven t and since we're star inference really brooks range like that
inference really brooks range like that okay in this claim that this is right
好的，这是正确的说法，不正确，这是一个近似值
okay in this claim that this is right no it's not right it's an approximation
no it's not right it's an approximation that's what variation of variational
那就是变分近似的变化
that's what variation of variational approximations are about they are
approximations are about they are approximate methods all right so we
好的近似方法，所以我们将这个后验分解为
approximate methods all right so we factorize this posterior to look like
factorize this posterior to look like this I asked you last time I'm not gonna
这是我上次问你的，这次我不会问你
this I asked you last time I'm not gonna ask you this time you're going to get
ask you this time you're going to get there another headache so the each of
还有另一个令人头疼的地方，所以这些分布中的每一个都在
there another headache so the each of these distributions in the in the in the
these distributions in the in the in the in the factorization so for example the
在分解中，例如，α的T的对数基本上是
in the factorization so for example the log of T of alpha is basically the
log of T of alpha is basically the expectation of the joining of black
期望黑色液体相对于所有其他液体的加入
expectation of the joining of black liquid with respect to all the other
liquid with respect to all the other parameters in this case since I'm
这种情况下的参数，因为我正在计算Q鹅肝
parameters in this case since I'm calculating Q foie gras the other
calculating Q foie gras the other parameters is W okay so if you need to
参数没问题，因此如果您需要在代数中做，则需要扩展
parameters is W okay so if you need to do in the algebra you need to expand the
do in the algebra you need to expand the joint log likelihood tell me the terms
联合对数似然法告诉我依赖于alpha和逆项的项
joint log likelihood tell me the terms that depend on alpha and inverse terms
that depend on alpha and inverse terms anything that has W you have to take an
任何具有W的东西，您都必须对W有所期望，因此，如果您
anything that has W you have to take an expectation with respect to W so if you
expectation with respect to W so if you plug in P alpha gamma distribution
插入日志的P alpha伽玛分布
plug in P alpha gamma distribution that's the log
that's the log this is a Gaussian easy to calculate so
这是一个易于计算的高斯函数，因此您需要对W进行转置W的期望
this is a Gaussian easy to calculate so you need expectation of W transpose W
you need expectation of W transpose W and then she makes professional public
然后，如果您接受高斯和
and then she makes professional public here right if you take in Gaussian and
here right if you take in Gaussian and you take the logs you supposed to get an
您拿起了您本应该对Bobby有所期待的原木，以及为什么它没有
you take the logs you supposed to get an expectation of Bobby also why it's not
expectation of Bobby also why it's not there I mean just visually realize I
我的意思是，从视觉上意识到我没有看到W的期望
there I mean just visually realize I don't see an expectation of W there
don't see an expectation of W there right waist up because yes
右腰向上，因为是的
为什么不期望W
don't see an expectation of W there right waist up because yes
why don't in expectation of W
好的，谢谢你，我的意思是我的东西正确
thank you all right I mean something right in my
all right I mean something right in my eyes looks wrong I have to think myself
眼睛看起来不对劲，我必须考虑一下自己，这样也很好，
eyes looks wrong I have to think myself so it's good that your things up too and
so it's good that your things up too and you say oh he's paid all right but it's
你说哦，他还清所有款项，但这显然不是一个错误，所以当
you say oh he's paid all right but it's obviously not a mistake okay so when
obviously not a mistake okay so when remember the constant terms are things
记住常数项是要依赖的东西，例如也许只是我在这里
remember the constant terms are things to depend for example maybe just me here
to depend for example maybe just me here and there constant times really and we
确实有固定的时间，我们不在乎，因为这是分布
and there constant times really and we don't care because this is distribution
don't care because this is distribution on alpha the only way she will keep this
在Alpha上，她保留此唯一方法是因为您要放置Alpha，所以
on alpha the only way she will keep this is because you want to place alpha so
is because you want to place alpha so you can email you see you can combine
您可以发送电子邮件给您，看到您可以将此日志双点组合在一起，就可以
you can email you see you can combine this log double dot there you can
this log double dot there you can combine this constant however this term
结合这个常数，但是这个术语乘以alpha，基本上就是你得到的
combine this constant however this term times alpha and basically what you get
times alpha and basically what you get is the log of it when you gamma
是您使用更新参数进行伽玛分布时的日志，因此
is the log of it when you gamma distribution with updated parameters so
distribution with updated parameters so the posterior looks like this and
后部看起来像这样，实际上您可以看到其中之一
the posterior looks like this and effectively you can see that one of the
effectively you can see that one of the reasons someone is using a gamma
有人对Alpha使用伽玛分布的原因真的是因为
reasons someone is using a gamma distribution for alpha is really because
distribution for alpha is really because I mean the approximate variation of
我的意思是分布cos alpha的近似变化是共轭的
I mean the approximate variation of distribution cos alpha is the conjugate
distribution cos alpha is the conjugate it comes basically to be an advantage of
它基本上是我们帮助的pyro系数的优势
it comes basically to be an advantage of the coefficients of the pyro we help out
the coefficients of the pyro we help out right before we only have this odd
就在我们只有这个奇数正数为0之前，您添加了这个不错的
right before we only have this odd positive be 0 now you added this nice
positive be 0 now you added this nice thing so it's pretty nuts ok even gets
事情，所以这很不错，甚至可以得到一个近似值，并加入Sparkle
thing so it's pretty nuts ok even gets an approximation get Sparkle join
an approximation get Sparkle join log-likelihood he the antibodies
对数似然他的抗体基本上是直截了当的，但是我侵蚀了
log-likelihood he the antibodies basically straight forward but I eroded
basically straight forward but I eroded fear rather not having these summations
担心而不是没有这些求和，我以矩阵向量形式编写了它
fear rather not having these summations I wrote this in a matrix vector forms
I wrote this in a matrix vector forms introducing the design matrix P that
引入涉及计算的基本函数的设计矩阵P
introducing the design matrix P that involves the basis functions calculated
involves the basis functions calculated at each of the given data points right
在设计矩阵右侧的每个给定数据点处，仅在值处
at each of the given data points right of the design matrix and just the values
of the design matrix and just the values of the function that we have given of
给定输入点的功能，所以这是一个
of the function that we have given of the given input points so this is a
the given input points so this is a Gaussian can see square you can see
高斯可以看到正方形，也可以看到W中的线性项，因此，如果您完成了
Gaussian can see square you can see linear term in W so if you complete the
linear term in W so if you complete the square again you get a Gaussian
再次平方，您会得到类似于我们开始之前的高斯曲线，但是
square again you get a Gaussian similar to the prior we started but with
similar to the prior we started but with updated parameters and I emphasize since
更新了参数，我强调，因为即使在
updated parameters and I emphasize since maybe you haven't seen this even in the
maybe you haven't seen this even in the context of
简单贝叶斯分析甚至是上下文
context of simple Bayesian analysis or even
simple Bayesian analysis or even expected and you shall depend on me well
期望，您将完全依靠我，您知道计算会给您一个
expected and you shall depend on me well you know calculation will give you an
you know calculation will give you an alcove it up here we did the expectation
把它凹进去，我们做了利润的预期
alcove it up here we did the expectation of profit okay
of profit okay there is no expectation of beta because
没有期望的beta版本，因为我在这里提到了更大的范围，
there is no expectation of beta because here I'm taking bigger as I mentioned to
here I'm taking bigger as I mentioned to become stock but I saw something that
变成库存，但如果您查看例如，我看到了一些精确的信息
become stock but I saw something that precise if you look for example in in
precise if you look for example in in the variation of expression for W you
W的表达式变化，您在这里注意到能够计算
the variation of expression for W you notice here to be able to compute this
notice here to be able to compute this you need to know the expectation of
您需要知道alpha的期望并知道
you need to know the expectation of alpha and to know the expectation of
alpha and to know the expectation of alpha right
如果您需要知道期望的阿尔法
alpha right if you need to know the expectation of
if you need to know the expectation of lambda transpose gamma so this is an
lambda转置伽马，所以这是一个迭代过程，实际上在某些情况下
lambda transpose gamma so this is an iterative process and actually in some
iterative process and actually in some books they because this sort of mimics
预订他们是因为这种模仿了期望最大化过程
books they because this sort of mimics the expectation maximization process
the expectation maximization process right you say do this update that and
对，你说做这个更新并插入它，所以你会在很多书中
right you say do this update that and plug in it so in lots of books you will
plug in it so in lots of books you will see the presentation on this as here is
请参阅此演示文稿，因为这是历史，这是m步，但这是
see the presentation on this as here is the history here is the m-step but it's
the history here is the m-step but it's really slightly different okay
确实有点不同，但是我知道很多机器学习
really slightly different okay but I know this lots of machine learning
but I know this lots of machine learning books they give this algorithms as if
书中，他们给出了这种算法，就好像您可以细细管教
books they give this algorithms as if there were you can mister very important
there were you can mister very important step various approximations so the exact
步进各种近似值，以便精确地后验，因此，如果您想对不起，
step various approximations so the exact posterior so if you want I'm sorry this
posterior so if you want I'm sorry this the traditional distribution right the
传统的分配权预测的后验分布因此
the traditional distribution right the prediction posterior distribution so
prediction posterior distribution so once you train the system you say now at
训练完系统后，您现在要在给定的XI上说，想知道
once you train the system you say now at the given X I want to know what the
the given X I want to know what the response is I'm taking the response yet
回应是我正在接受回应，但尚未成为扫描程序，这赏金是
response is I'm taking the response yet to be scanner and this bounty is the
to be scanner and this bounty is the data right so that's the prolific
正确的数据，因此这是多产的后验，因此基本上是
data right so that's the prolific posterior so that's basically the
posterior so that's basically the likelihood
如果您知道W，您为什么会得到
likelihood why would you get if you if you know W
why would you get if you if you know W times the posterior what all the
乘以后验是什么，所有的参数都被整合出来，
times the posterior what all the parameters are integrated out and the
parameters are integrated out and the King radium here is we are not going to
镭王在这里是我们不会插入实际的后路
King radium here is we are not going to plug in the actual posterior
plug in the actual posterior you actually plug in the variational
你实际上插入了变分近似值，这就是你的罂粟好吗
you actually plug in the variational approximation which is your poppy okay
现在确切的Pastino是非常随和的高斯，所以我们可以
now is the exact pastino is is very easygoing Gaussian so we could about
easygoing Gaussian so we could about this but here we demonstrate this is an
这个，但是在这里我们演示这是一个例子，所以您插入qw，这是
this but here we demonstrate this is an example so you plug in qw and this is
example so you plug in qw and this is the marginalization you remember you
边缘化，你记得你有最好的东西，拍卖有
the marginalization you remember you have something best the auction has a
have something best the auction has a mean that's a linear function of gamma
就是说，这是伽玛nu的线性函数，然后你有x应该
mean that's a linear function of gamma nu you know and then you have x should
nu you know and then you have x should not be an integration of that view right
不能整合这种观点，所以这确实是一个边际
not be an integration of that view right so this is really a marginal
so this is really a marginal distribution on P and if you look at the
分布在P上，如果您查看进度，方便的原始系统I
distribution on P and if you look at the progress convenient origin systems I
progress convenient origin systems I told you to have them perfect in your
告诉你让它们完美地放在你的书桌上
told you to have them perfect in your desk all right
desk all right look at them every day because these
每天看看它们，因为您每天都会使用这些方程式十
look at them every day because these equations you use them every day ten
equations you use them every day ten times so you don't have to search okay
时间，因此您不必搜索就可以了，因此，如果将它们插入电源，便可以查看它们
times so you don't have to search okay so you look at them if you plug them in
so you look at them if you plug them in and basically you get another Gaussian
基本上你得到另一个高斯，你可以看到方差
and basically you get another Gaussian and you can see the the variance so of
and you can see the the variance so of course dependent on X so it varies with
当然取决于X，所以它随X的变化而变化，如果再放一遍，一切都会好起来的
course dependent on X so it varies with X and if you put again things okay
X and if you put again things okay you will notice again that this matrix
您会再次注意到，该矩阵为n取决于您知道期望值
you will notice again that this matrix is n depends on you know the expectation
is n depends on you know the expectation of alpha and the design matrix P okay so
α和设计矩阵P的确定，所以很显然是对功率的期望
of alpha and the design matrix P okay so obviously the expectation of power power
obviously the expectation of power power we know it assuming we have computed the
假设我们已经计算了的变分近似，我们就知道了
we know it assuming we have computed the the variational approximation for of the
the variational approximation for of the posterior Palko okay the thing that I'm
后方的帕尔科好吧，我要很快提醒你的是
posterior Palko okay the thing that I'm going to remind you very quickly is
going to remind you very quickly is every time the devil external influence
每次魔鬼的外部影响是波动的
every time the devil external influence is a fluctuation
is a fluctuation you always have to verify that the
您始终必须验证计算是否正确，并且唯一
you always have to verify that the calculations are correct and the only
calculations are correct and the only way you can do this is by calculating
您可以通过计算下界并显示
way you can do this is by calculating the lower bound and showing that the
the lower bound and showing that the lower bound in crease is basically
如果分解的话，折痕的下界基本上是单调的
lower bound in crease is basically monotonically if decomposition does
monotonically if decomposition does increase monotonically
单调增加有问题吗
increase monotonically there is a problem okay
there is a problem okay so I remind you the long vault is the
所以我提醒您，长期以来的金库是对
so I remind you the long vault is the expectation with respect to the
expectation with respect to the variation of distribution chill of the
联合似然的名称的分布寒气的变化除以
variation of distribution chill of the name of the joint likelihood divided by
name of the joint likelihood divided by the valuation of this depletion so it's
消耗量的估值，因此，如果您扩展其中一个
the valuation of this depletion so it's written like that if you expand one of
written like that if you expand one of the parents you know everything so it's
父母你什么都知道，所以更重要的是，你刚刚把它换成新的
the parents you know everything so it's more it's a block right you just put new
more it's a block right you just put new things but you know what if I asked you
事情，但是你知道如果我要你再推一下，把这个给我一半的话
things but you know what if I asked you to push again and give me this in half
to push again and give me this in half an hour I bet most probably none of you
一个小时，我敢打赌，你们中的任何一个都不会完成它，好吧，你的孩子和我一起
an hour I bet most probably none of you will complete it okay your baby with me
will complete it okay your baby with me all right absolutely okay
好的，绝对正确，你们中一个人会完成的原因
all right absolutely okay and the reason one of you will complete
and the reason one of you will complete it because you can see take you out so
因为您可以看到带您出去，所以您可以做一个非常代数的代数
it because you can see take you out so you do the algebra in a very so you look
you do the algebra in a very so you look at them you say here easy no it's not
在他们那里对他们说容易，不，这并不容易，因为如果您尝试在自己的计算机上执行此操作
at them you say here easy no it's not easy because if you try to do it on your
easy because if you try to do it on your own for another problem you will mess it
拥有另一个问题，您会把它弄乱，所以有一个教育意义
own for another problem you will mess it up okay so there is an educational
up okay so there is an educational purpose of doing this for simple
这样做的目的是为了解决诸如回归问题之类的简单问题
purpose of doing this for simple problems like a regression problem
problems like a regression problem because you know if you do all the songs
因为您知道您是否完成了有关该插件的所有歌曲，并且插件和插件
because you know if you do all the songs about the plug-in and plug in and plug
about the plug-in and plug in and plug in and then connect by the miracle of
然后通过网状奇迹连接到最终答案是什么？
in and then connect by the miracle of nets to what is the final answer do I
nets to what is the final answer do I have a final answer somewhere
在某个地方有最终答案
拒绝相信Alec您的订阅，因为最终的答案是
nets to what is the final answer do I have a final answer somewhere
defy belief the subscribe with Alec you because the final answer comes to be
拒绝相信Alec您的订阅，因为最终的答案是
because the final answer comes to be pretty nice somebody ate my slide okay
很好，有人吃了我的幻灯片，好吧，反正在这里，但是当你
pretty nice somebody ate my slide okay so anyways here right but when you you
so anyways here right but when you you did a very nice answer okay
做了一个很好的答案，好了，故事结束了，这是这个
did a very nice answer okay end of story okay and this is this
end of story okay and this is this rebound in connection so for example if
连接反弹，例如，如果您正在集成并且您有一个
rebound in connection so for example if you're doing integration and you have a
you're doing integration and you have a bunch of data and you say you know let's
一堆数据，您说您知道，假设您在这种情况下使用多项式
bunch of data and you say you know let's say you use polynomials in this case you
say you use polynomials in this case you say what's the other of polynomials that
说出我需要使用的多项式中的其他多项式更好地表示
say what's the other of polynomials that I need to use you better represent the
I need to use you better represent the data you know I'd be much more
你知道的数据我更有可能是麦克斯韦的论点说
data you know I'd be much more likelihood Maxwell's argument saying
因为它会不断增加，但是你永远不会消失，所以随着变化
because the will keep increasing but you will never fade okay so with variation
will never fade okay so with variation influenced and using these lower bounds
影响并使用案例的这些下限，您可以在这里看到它说
influenced and using these lower bounds of the case and you can see here it says
of the case and you can see here it says M equal trees what explains the data
M个相等的树解释了数据还可以，我想我们已经讨论过了
M equal trees what explains the data okay and I think we already discussed
okay and I think we already discussed and I may come back today also if you do
如果您确实注意到选举权，并且我提出了，那么我今天也可能会回来
and I may come back today also if you do notice election right and you put let's
notice election right and you put let's say some vehicle prior over the space of
说一些车辆本质上在多项式数量的空间上
say some vehicle prior over the space of the number of polynomials in essence
the number of polynomials in essence this this is you know very you know this
这是你知道的，你知道这个人口有效地给你
this this is you know very you know this population effectively gives you an
population effectively gives you an approximation to the posterior of the
近似于模型的后验，所以基本上这没什么
approximation to the posterior of the model right so basically this is nothing
model right so basically this is nothing else but the posterior of the model with
否则，当您知道L 7等于3时，模型的后验与
else but the posterior of the model with when you know L 7 equal to three okay so
when you know L 7 equal to three okay so this is a very nice way to do model
这是选择模型的好方法
this is a very nice way to do model selection
selection right and this is a very nice picture
对的，这是一张非常不错的照片，很抱歉，我的意思是没有照片
right and this is a very nice picture from sorry I mean no picture were just
from sorry I mean no picture were just really a little awkward around this
围绕此计算确实有点尴尬
really a little awkward around this calculations run the matter of using the
calculations run the matter of using the Kevin leftists t-bolts so basically on
凯文·左派（t。
Kevin leftists t-bolts so basically on the customer choice you the map of
the customer choice you the map of inaction so a calculation of the
无所作为，因此计算了这些模型的后验
inaction so a calculation of the posterior of these models of the
posterior of these models of the universe of polynomials given some data
给定多项式的宇宙给定一些数据，在这里我们有五个数据点，
universe of polynomials given some data which here we have five data points and
which here we have five data points and you can see that very few data the metro
您会看到很少的数据就是您的地铁自行车贬值参考
you can see that very few data the metro bicycle devaluation reference that's you
bicycle devaluation reference that's you you know what use the lower of the
你知道什么用多项式的较低者好吗最低的模型是什么
you know what use the lower of the polynomial okay the lowest model is what
polynomial okay the lowest model is what you need but when you increase the
您需要，但是当您增加数据量时，例如在这里
you need but when you increase the number of data for example here it
number of data for example here it immediately puts the posterior on m
立即将后验放在m等于3的极低点，它告诉您
immediately puts the posterior on m equal to three very low and it tells you
equal to three very low and it tells you not select the model with M equal to two
不选择M等于2的模型，此方法是经验Baggett的
not select the model with M equal to two this method is empirical Baggett's
this method is empirical Baggett's method basically okay and this is what
方法基本上还可以，这就是您所知道的产品，我们提出了这个问题
method basically okay and this is what you know products we put the question in
you know products we put the question in the tall they are reading machine
他们正在阅读机器学习的高个子，这基本上是
the tall they are reading machine learning looks this is basically the
learning looks this is basically the evidence approximation it doesn't do as
证据近似，效果也不佳
evidence approximation it doesn't do as well
well so you can see for example in the
因此，例如，您可以在观察证据中看到
so you can see for example in the evidence of observation here it puts a
evidence of observation here it puts a lot on this posterior for m equal to R
这个后验的很多，m等于R，但是这里基本上可以说是当前
lot on this posterior for m equal to R but here basically tell mostly currently
but here basically tell mostly currently distributed we have a few data because
分布的我们有一些数据，因为在那种情况下是先验数据
distributed we have a few data because in that case is the prior that dominate
in that case is the prior that dominate the
这个后验这里真的没有
this posterior here there's no really such a thing so this is not cool evasion
这样的事情，所以这不是很酷的逃避，而是这个很酷的逃避
such a thing so this is not cool evasion but this cool evasion
好的，我将要执行此操作，但是我提到您可以扩展此类型
but this cool evasion
all right I am going to do this but I mentioned that you can expand this type
好的，我将要执行此操作，但是我提到您可以扩展此类型
mentioned that you can expand this type of calculations when you take this
您在似然模型中采用这种精度时的计算
of calculations when you take this precision in the likelihood model also
precision in the likelihood model also to be around the body moon right so you
在身体的月亮周围，所以你可以在上面放一个钳子，
to be around the body moon right so you can put a plier on that and in you know
can put a plier on that and in you know you can basically repeat all the
您基本上可以重复所有计算，就可以计算出
you can basically repeat all the calculations and you can calculate so if
calculations and you can calculate so if you put a gamma prior on beta you can
您将伽玛值放在beta之前，就可以计算出近似的后验值，但是
you put a gamma prior on beta you can calculate an approximate posterior but
calculate an approximate posterior but this launched a gamma and you can see
这启动了伽玛，您可以看到公式非常好地出现在
this launched a gamma and you can see the formulas come very nicely in the
the formulas come very nicely in the very close call you know and and the
您知道非常近距离的通话，答案实际上并不重要，
very close call you know and and the answer is really nothing significant and
answer is really nothing significant and you can actually calculate the
您实际上可以计算出预测分布，而并非
you can actually calculate the predictive distribution and it's not
predictive distribution and it's not surprising actually for example you look
实际上令人惊讶，例如，您看到方差是相同的
surprising actually for example you look at the variance comes to be identical
at the variance comes to be identical with the previous result but this kind
与之前的结果相同，但您对这种领导者有beta的期望
with the previous result but this kind of leader you have expectation of beta
of leader you have expectation of beta okay so so much of the answers really
好吧，这么多的答案真的是可以预期的好吧好吧好吧
okay so so much of the answers really sort of are expected okay all right okay
sort of are expected okay all right okay so I'm going to switch now lecture and
所以我现在要转讲课，我要回来提醒我
so I'm going to switch now lecture and I'm going to come back remind me to
I'm going to come back remind me to write 16 after we we move from this
我们从这里移开后写16
还有非常基本的问题，所以我们将讨论一些
I'm going to come back remind me to write 16 after we we move from this
and very fundamental problem okay so we're going to discuss something that
还有非常基本的问题，所以我们将讨论一些
we're going to discuss something that looks a trivial to lots of you but you
对于很多人来说看起来微不足道，但是如果您搜索文献，您会发现
looks a trivial to lots of you but you will if you search the literature you
will if you search the literature you find a lots of Papers written because
找到很多书面论文，因为这是一个非常根本的问题
find a lots of Papers written because it's an extremely fundamental problem
it's an extremely fundamental problem that comes everywhere so the idea here
到处都有，所以这里的想法是我们正在谈论混合
that comes everywhere so the idea here is we are talking about a mixture of
is we are talking about a mixture of gaussians and what interest to do
高斯以及对近似贝叶斯推断感兴趣的兴趣是什么。
gaussians and what interest to do approximate Bayesian inference for a
approximate Bayesian inference for a mixture of gaussians so what does that
高斯混合体，那么这意味着什么，您知道您知道自己从
mixture of gaussians so what does that mean you know you know become from a
mean you know you know become from a mixture of the two three four five
我正在做的两个三四五高斯的混合体对你来说我没有
mixture of the two three four five gaussians I'm doing have to you I don't
gaussians I'm doing have to you I don't tell you generate the data and I'm
告诉你生成数据，我告诉你去计算
tell you generate the data and I'm telling you go and calculate the
telling you go and calculate the posterior of the mixing components and
混合成分的后验，并为其成分计算平均值和
posterior of the mixing components and for its component compute the mean and
for its component compute the mean and the variance okay simple ways to do and
差异可以做的简单方法，所以我假装你有
the variance okay simple ways to do and so I'm going to pretend that you have
so I'm going to pretend that you have never seen this problem before in other
以前从未以其他方式见过这个问题，而您不知道其他解决方案好吗
never seen this problem before in other ways you don't know other solutions okay
ways you don't know other solutions okay so we're gonna concentrate on variation
所以我们要专注于兴趣对象的变化
so we're gonna concentrate on variation of the interest object okay and again
of the interest object okay and again this is very fundamental in machine
这在机器学习中非常重要，它无处不在，
this is very fundamental in machine learning it comes everywhere and
learning it comes everywhere and actually this concept of gaussians you
实际上，这个高斯概念你甚至可以把另一个世界变成一个高斯
actually this concept of gaussians you can even put another world that make it
can even put another world that make it mixed up thousand processes okay we will
混合了数千个流程好吧，我们将在本课程中不进行讨论，并且
mixed up thousand processes okay we will not discuss that in this course and
not discuss that in this course and actually to make it even more relevant
实际上使其与研究混合物的类型更加相关
actually to make it even more relevant to research the sort of mixture you can
to research the sort of mixture you can say infinite mixture of Gaussian
说高斯过程的无限混合，所以基本上您可以进行排序
say infinite mixture of Gaussian processes so basically you can do sort
processes so basically you can do sort of relevance determination and trial
确定性和试探性无限知识组成部分，并让
of relevance determination and trial infinite knowledge component and let
infinite knowledge component and let this analysis figure out which ones are
该分析可以找出哪些名称可以，并且不必
this analysis figure out which ones are named it okay and it doesn't have to be
named it okay and it doesn't have to be gaussians can be Gaussian processes and
高斯可以是高斯过程，这需要是最近的
gaussians can be Gaussian processes and this needs to be a very recent sort of
this needs to be a very recent sort of relevant results basically that some of
相关结果基本上就是你们中的一些
relevant results basically that some of you
you or someone feel their interest to
或有人觉得他们有兴趣进行研究，所以我们实际上讨论了
or someone feel their interest to research okay so we actually discuss the
research okay so we actually discuss the problem no need to read anything so
问题，无需阅读任何内容，因此请记住，我们有以下发现：
problem no need to read anything so remember that we have observations of
remember that we have observations of some de vita XM it's data just relate
我称之为de vita XM的数据与2080年的数据相关且有价值
some de vita XM it's data just relate and valuable of 2080 with it that I call
and valuable of 2080 with it that I call its GM so you can think of Zn being a
它的转基因，所以您可以将Zn视为标签主体，这就是
its GM so you can think of Zn being a label body blighters here it is this
label body blighters here it is this component of it is Gaussian or web
它的组成部分是高斯（Gaussian）或高斯上方的网络浏览器，因此
component of it is Gaussian or web browser above Gaussian so that's the
browser above Gaussian so that's the late environment it's the you know it's
后期环境是您知道的这是两个高斯人的额外信息
late environment it's the you know it's extra information of two gaussians it's
extra information of two gaussians it's version will have its own mean and
版本将具有自己的均值和方差，并且该局部
version will have its own mean and variance all right and this local
variance all right and this local variables will be defined through some
变量将通过一些礼貌的方式定义，而不是通过参数
variables will be defined through some polite other than the parameters of the
polite other than the parameters of the drive or the cold clear pie and I will
驱动器或冷气派，我将在幻灯片上为您提供详细信息，
drive or the cold clear pie and I will give you the specifics on the slides to
give you the specifics on the slides to come so their joint likelihood so this
来吧，他们共同的可能性，所以这是潜伏的观察
come so their joint likelihood so this is the observation this the latent
is the observation this the latent variables these are the various
变量这些是定义先验条件的各种参数
variables these are the various parameters to define the priors
parameters to define the priors so basically you can save this
因此，基本上，您也可以图形化地保存大写字母
so basically you can save this capitalization also graphically the
capitalization also graphically the rezoning of likelihood would be the
似然的重新分区将是x在给定C和镧的情况下的概率
rezoning of likelihood would be the probability of x given C and lanthanum
probability of x given C and lanthanum the probability of Z given by the
Z的概率由新给定的lambda的概率和
the probability of Z given by the probability of new given lambda and the
probability of new given lambda and the probability of love so this is sort of a
爱情的几率，所以这有点像一个非常沉重，非常简单的图表，但是
probability of love so this is sort of a very heavy very simple graph but the
very heavy very simple graph but the calculation you will see it's not it's
计算，您会发现不是很痛苦
calculation you will see it's not it's painful
painful okay but it is a calculation that again
好的，但这是一种计算，如果再次执行此操作，您将感觉到
okay but it is a calculation that again if you do it once you will get the sense
if you do it once you will get the sense of what it is and how it works
它是什么以及如何运作的，所以在我看来，例如
of what it is and how it works okay so in my view for example in the
okay so in my view for example in the midst of noxious right if you put this
如果把这个关节放在有害的权利中间
midst of noxious right if you put this joint
joint replica together this comes to be
复制品一起成为高斯，如果条件作用一个
replica together this comes to be Gaussian and if a condition actions a
Gaussian and if a condition actions a young get a gout okay
年轻人会痛风好吗
条件很好，如果我整合拇指D好的，你不会走对的
Gaussian and if a condition actions a young get a gout okay
the condition excellency if I integrate thumbs D okay you're not gonna go right
条件很好，如果我整合拇指D好的，你不会走对的
thumbs D okay you're not gonna go right but the joint likelihood is a Gaussian
但是联合的可能性是高斯，这就是为什么我们运作良好，所以我想要
but the joint likelihood is a Gaussian and that's why we operate okay so I want
and that's why we operate okay so I want you to look at this distribution that
你看看这个分布，告诉我你了解什么，所以px
you to look at this distribution that tells me what you understand it so px
tells me what you understand it so px given Z looks like that then you tell me
鉴于Z看起来像那样，那么你告诉我一切都不好
given Z looks like that then you tell me everything is not okay
我的意思是我需要每学期写一次，所以给定Z时x的P
I mean I'm going to need to compute write this every term so P of x given Z
write this every term so P of x given Z and V other parameters is given like
和V其他参数是这样给出的，所以我有n个数据点，我有一个
and V other parameters is given like that so I have n data points I have a
that so I have n data points I have a mixed with K components so does this
与K成分混合在一起，这样才有意义，所以C和K采取什么-什么
mixed with K components so does this make sense so C and K takes what - what
make sense so C and K takes what - what is the one of the values in K takes Z so
是K中的值之一取Z，所以仅对每个数据点而言
is the one of the values in K takes Z so so for every data point right only
so for every data point right only assume this time see that product is
假设这次看到乘积将是高斯，那将是
assume this time see that product is going to be a Gaussian and that would be
going to be a Gaussian and that would be only for the K equals e and k equal to 1
仅当K等于e且k等于1时
only for the K equals e and k equal to 1 right
我们已经看到了大约一千次的面额，非常接近
we have seen this about the thousand times of denominated so close to a very
times of denominated so close to a very compact way of writing things everyone
每个人都可以的紧凑写作方式，您知道的我们最多
compact way of writing things everyone is in okay you know the most we listen
is in okay you know the most we listen this tapes from home because they have
这是家中的磁带，因为他们无事可做，才是真正的爱
this tapes from home because they have nothing else to do right is true love
nothing else to do right is true love maybe scream once or say something
也许尖叫一次或说些什么，所以他们认为我不是在和一个
maybe scream once or say something so they think that I'm not talking to a
so they think that I'm not talking to a wall alright because you know lots of
好吧，因为你知道很多教授喜欢自言自语
wall alright because you know lots of professors like talking to themselves
professors like talking to themselves alright so okay I can even pass you the
好吧，好吧，我什至可以把麦克风传给你，所以Z很奇怪，记得如此
alright so okay I can even pass you the microphone so weird so Z and remember so
microphone so weird so Z and remember so you know we are thinking about the next
你知道我们正在考虑下一个有人发现这种混合
you know we are thinking about the next another somebody find this mixing
another somebody find this mixing quotation spy and I want you to look at
报价间谍，我想让你看看这个，对我来说，我要么
quotation spy and I want you to look at this and to me it's okay that I'm either
this and to me it's okay that I'm either way we have it here remember every point
我们在这里拥有它的方式记住每个点xn3 Seussian，所以这是什么
way we have it here remember every point xn3 Seussian so so what is this here the
xn3 Seussian so so what is this here the player that I am using is so over all
我正在使用的播放器是如此，所以在所有数据点上，我都会写什么
player that I am using is so over all the data points I would write what is
the data points I would write what is this what is this conditional
这是给定PI的Z的条件分布是什么，所以它将
this what is this conditional distribution of Z given PI so it would
distribution of Z given PI so it would say at the given point and only one of
在给定的时间点说，并且只有其中一种情况是其中一种
say at the given point and only one of those things one of the one of the case
those things one of the one of the case this would be equal to one and this will
这将等于一，这会给你好吧
this would be equal to one and this will give you okay all right
嗨，那位球员将要添加剪辑直播
all right hi and that player is going to be adding a clip live okay
be adding a clip live okay and and that's what I mentioned that
这就是我提到的，该光盘可以轻松扩展到
and and that's what I mentioned that this a disc and easily extended to
this a disc and easily extended to infinite mixture of of gaussians by
高斯的无限混合，在这里用声明代替
infinite mixture of of gaussians by substituting here by using a declare
substituting here by using a declare process basically to do a special user
流程基本上是做一个特殊的用户声明优先服务列表的
process basically to do a special user declare prior service list the
declare prior service list the parameters on cozinha wants to remember
cozinha上的参数要记住表示法还可以，您可能会说为什么
parameters on cozinha wants to remember of the notation okay and you may say why
of the notation okay and you may say why did the clip prior because based is
事先做了剪辑，因为基于将使所有后代成为
did the clip prior because based is going to make all the posteriors to be
going to make all the posteriors to be nothing else but updates basically the
只是更新了您所分配的分布参数而已
nothing else but updates basically the parameters of the distributions that you
parameters of the distributions that you see right now so basically these are
现在看，所以基本上这些是共轭先验好，所以他们要去
see right now so basically these are conjugate priors okay so they are going
conjugate priors okay so they are going to make the algebra easy okay the
为了使代数变得容易，参数的意思是亚特兰大，你可能有
to make the algebra easy okay the parameters mean atlanta and you may have
parameters mean atlanta and you may have seen this for evaluation you may not
看过这个用于评估，您可能还没有看过，所以基本上我们写这个
seen this for evaluation you may not have seen it so basically we write this
have seen it so basically we write this as a product over all the components of
作为产品的不足，所有缺陷的所有组成部分
as a product over all the components of a deficient all right with the lots of
a deficient all right with the lots of unknown parameters but you know here the
参数未知，但是您知道这里的精度取决于精度
unknown parameters but you know here the precision depends the precision this
precision depends the precision this condition of the precision and then the
精度的条件，然后是精度，我们将储备分配
condition of the precision and then the precision we put a reserve distribution
precision we put a reserve distribution this is you know in one dimension you
这是你知道的一个维度，你知道这看起来会是什么样子
this is you know in one dimension you know how this will look like this will
know how this will look like this will be devoid of Gaussian and what will not
没有高斯，那么精确度会是什么呢？
be devoid of Gaussian and what will not be for the precision would did we say
be for the precision would did we say who uses a prior
谁使用先验
在回归问题下我应该成为什么？
be for the precision would did we say who uses a prior
what should I become below the regression problem what was the point of
在回归问题下我应该成为什么？
regression problem what was the point of the precision he was a memo said the
巫师先生说，他是备忘录的精确度。以任务为基础
the precision he was a memo said the wizard mr. mission based as a
wizard mr. mission based as a generalization to multivariate variables
我对伽玛分布权的多元变量的概括
generalization to multivariate variables of the gamma distribution right I mean
of the gamma distribution right I mean if you think you know the wizard
如果您认为自己知道向导分发是某种分发
if you think you know the wizard distribution is sort of a distribution
distribution is sort of a distribution although symmetric positive-definite
虽然对称正定矩阵可以很好的分布我
although symmetric positive-definite matrices okay very nice distribution I
matrices okay very nice distribution I me if you think distribution of a matrix
我，如果您认为矩阵的分布较少，那么对称
me if you think distribution of a matrix is less and what about symmetric
is less and what about symmetric positive matrices here is the Parthians
正矩阵在这里是Parthians lambda k好的，所以这再次没问题
positive matrices here is the Parthians lambda k okay so this is again all right
lambda k okay so this is again all right so when you have that mean and precision
因此，当您具有未知的均值和精度时，可以这样写：
so when you have that mean and precision unknown okay you write like that if
unknown okay you write like that if actually he did not use the precision
实际上，他没有使用精度，而是使用方差，这可以
actually he did not use the precision but use the variance this can you can
but use the variance this can you can write the same thing but instead of a
写同样的东西，但是代替了向导分发，而是放了英文
write the same thing but instead of a wizard distribution you put an English
wizard distribution you put an English wizard distribution
向导分发还可以，所以您可以使用所用的东西进行操作
wizard distribution okay so what you use you can manipulate
okay so what you use you can manipulate you one way or another but using here
您以一种或另一种方式使用，但是使用此处的精确度使代数方式是您
you one way or another but using here precision makes the algebra way is you
precision makes the algebra way is you so there is a lecture for notes to start
因此，有一个关于笔记的讲座，它以许多私有参数开始，所以
so there is a lecture for notes to start with lots of private parameters right so
with lots of private parameters right so you can plug in some reasonable value so
您可以插入一些合理的值，所以我在这里指出我们中的一些人，所以我们需要
you can plug in some reasonable value so I indicate some of us here so so we need
I indicate some of us here so so we need to perhaps make now the posterior of
也许现在使这个巨大的未知数成为后验，
to perhaps make now the posterior of this massive unknowns and those are
this massive unknowns and those are those are the positives of the latent
这些是潜在变量z的正值，下一个的原始值
those are the positives of the latent variable z the pristine of the next
variable z the pristine of the next coefficient spy the prestige of the
系数间谍手段的威望亩和记住艾米是一个向量
coefficient spy the prestige of the means mu and remember amy is a vector
means mu and remember amy is a vector but the components are having less of
但是组件的所有这些都没那么多，对此的追求
but the components are having less of those all right and the pursue of this
those all right and the pursue of this variance is long time and i have a lot
变化是很长的时间，我有很多事情，所以这有点像
variance is long time and i have a lot of okay so this is sort of a written in
of okay so this is sort of a written in a compact way and the only sort of time
紧凑的方式和唯一的时间，当我要糊涂时，我通常是这样
a compact way and the only sort of time i when i'm gonna baste i'm normally this
i when i'm gonna baste i'm normally this is cubes if you apply give them you
是立方体，如果您申请给他们您Planta，因为如果我的意思是至少
is cubes if you apply give them you planta because if we I mean as a minimum
planta because if we I mean as a minimum to expect to get the conjugate you know
期望得到共轭，如果您期望得到一个具有
to expect to get the conjugate you know if you expect a bit of a stated that has
if you expect a bit of a stated that has the phone of the prior oats obviously
以前燕麦的电话显然会让您说看
the phone of the prior oats obviously you're going to get let's say looking at
you're going to get let's say looking at you know long time you're going to get
你知道很长一段时间你会得到一些分解给你
you know long time you're going to get some factorization of you given long
some factorization of you given long papyrus evaluations division of real
纸莎草纸实时评估部门，因此您希望保持这种状态
papyrus evaluations division of real time so you want to keep them like that
time so you want to keep them like that together otherwise you're not going to
在一起，否则您将不会利用这些共轭先验
together otherwise you're not going to take advantage of these conjugate priors
take advantage of these conjugate priors that you use okay so this will it be
您可以使用，所以这与电灼不同
that you use okay so this will it be different from the cauterization this is
different from the cauterization this is going to pop your eyes and interesting
会突然睁大你的眼睛，看到有趣的东西，所以基本上你可以认为是对的
going to pop your eyes and interesting to see so basically you can think right
to see so basically you can think right but we optimized it in one of the
但我们在其中有一组变量的一个因素中对其进行了优化，
but we optimized it in one of the factors we have a group of variables and
factors we have a group of variables and there's a potential reaction in
变化水平会有潜在的反应，您会这样做吗？
there's a potential reaction in variation levels will you do this for a
variation levels will you do this for a purpose okay
目的好吧，您将要更新一组
purpose okay you are going to update the group of
you are going to update the group of values together
价值观在一起
好吧，尝试保持假设，如果你给一个标志你所理解的
you are going to update the group of values together
okay so and try to keep taking assuming if you give a sign what you understand
好吧，尝试保持假设，如果你给一个标志你所理解的
if you give a sign what you understand nothing and in that case I will click
什么也没有，在这种情况下，我将单击两次，所以Z的数字K正确为
nothing and in that case I will click twice so the number K of Z alright as
twice so the number K of Z alright as the optimal distribution is the
最优分配是对所有
the optimal distribution is the expectation with respect to all the
expectation with respect to all the other variables
联合的对数的其他变量Jaime Lanka
other variables Jaime Lanka of the log of the joint of
Jaime Lanka of the log of the joint of likelihood right okay so when one of
可能吧，所以当其中之一时，我们将扩展所有这些
likelihood right okay so when one of these we're going to expand this all
these we're going to expand this all right and keep on in the terms the
正确并继续保持依存关系，让我们看看是什么类型
right and keep on in the terms the dependency all right let's see what type
dependency all right let's see what type of distribution it comes out so the only
分布的结果，所以唯一依赖于Z的时间就是这样
of distribution it comes out so the only times that depend on Z is from this
times that depend on Z is from this condition of Z given the mixing
给定混合系数，Z的条件，这可能是Patel可以
condition of Z given the mixing coefficients and this likely Patel okay
coefficients and this likely Patel okay this depends on a and PI so these
这取决于a和PI，因此这些期望值受到尊重
this depends on a and PI so these expectations with respected by which
expectations with respected by which depends on in Atlanta so the expectation
取决于亚特兰大，所以期望是对亚特兰大的尊重
depends on in Atlanta so the expectation is with respect in the Atlanta possible
is with respect in the Atlanta possible never share okay
永远都不会同意，我以前一直坚持要你的原因
never share okay and the reason I used to insist that you
and the reason I used to insist that you guys type this things in your homework
当你的时间很明显的时候，伙计们在你的家庭作业中输入这些东西
guys type this things in your homework when your time the answers obvious if
when your time the answers obvious if you do this by chance you you never gave
您是偶然地做到这一点的，您从未选择让它起作用的选项，
you do this by chance you you never gave option to make this to work you have a
option to make this to work you have a complete mess so if you take P of Z
完全是一团糟，所以如果您给定Z的给定值P等于Z
complete mess so if you take P of Z given pile given like this you take the
given pile given like this you take the likelihood you know like all this have
您可能知道所有这些都有以前的公式，所以您记得
likelihood you know like all this have the previous formulas so you remember
the previous formulas so you remember you will take it next year so it will be
您将在明年使用它，因此它将是PI的0倍，然后是
you will take it next year so it will be 0 times R over PI and then will be an
0 times R over PI and then will be an expectation with respect to PI and here
关于PI的期望值，这里我们将Z乘以
expectation with respect to PI and here we're going to have Z times the end of
we're going to have Z times the end of this with sigasi so obviously it going
与sigasi一起使用，因此很明显它会给Z或抛出相同的东西，
this with sigasi so obviously it going to give Z or throw the same thing and
to give Z or throw the same thing and that same thing is what you see here all
那件事就是你在这里看到的，好吧，这件事，这件事来自
that same thing is what you see here all right this comes this thing comes from
right this comes this thing comes from here and all of the stones come from
在这里，所有的石头都来自这个家伙的地方，你可以看到它吗
here and all of the stones come from where from this guy's you can you see it
where from this guy's you can you see it yes ok so this time wasted for
是的，好的，所以这次浪费了记忆因素，我们不在乎
yes ok so this time wasted for memorization factor we don't really care
memorization factor we don't really care about the cost of the time and okay and
关于时间的花费，还可以，而且他们花钱跳舞，因为现在
about the cost of the time and okay and and they are paying to dance because now
and they are paying to dance because now this level all depends on the
这个水平全取决于熔岩战斗的期望写什么
this level all depends on the expectation of lava fight a write what
expectation of lava fight a write what is the dimension where you have to be
是您必须感兴趣的维度，因此内容意味着
is the dimension where you have to be interested so the content is that means
interested so the content is that means you have to find the fluctuation for try
您必须找到波动来尝试完成这次的识别
you have to find the fluctuation for try to complete this time identifying the
to complete this time identifying the various of expression for tau the point
tau的各种表达方式，重点是您需要了解各种
various of expression for tau the point is you need to know the various
is you need to know the various approximation from you enter the joint
您输入的近似值基本上可以进入关节，所以我们还没有到那里
approximation from you enter the joint basically ok so we're not yet there
basically ok so we're not yet there so this is the result ok well mr. have
所以先生，这是好的结果。有赖于这些其他后代，但
so this is the result ok well mr. have depends on these other posteriors but
depends on these other posteriors but obviously you can immediately see that
显然，您可以立即看到该近似值的变化
obviously you can immediately see that this variation of approximation for the
this variation of approximation for the posterior of G it's basically written
G的后部，基本上就是你所有的力量Z写的好吗，记住什么
posterior of G it's basically written all of your power Z okay remember what
all of your power Z okay remember what was happened in the prior shared before
发生在先前共享中，在我们开始电路之前，发生了什么
was happened in the prior shared before when we started in circuit well what did
when we started in circuit well what did we have when we started it was by the
我们刚开始的时候是通过混合系数来的
we have when we started it was by the mixing coefficients okay
mixing coefficients okay there have five
有五个
好吧，所以如果你可以用等号写这个，你基本上就会知道
mixing coefficients okay there have five
all right so if you can write this with an equal sign you get basically you know
好吧，所以如果你可以用等号写这个，你基本上就会知道
an equal sign you get basically you know divided by the summation of this result
除以该结果对于每个数据点的总和
divided by the summation of this result for every data point there so
for every data point there so distribution looks like that which is
分布看起来与我们所解决的问题相同
distribution looks like that which is identical to the to the problem that we
identical to the to the problem that we started this equations to start with
从现在开始，我们已经观察到了白天的时间
started this equations to start with right now we have observed the day time
right now we have observed the day time we have updated the posterior of Z so
我们更新了Z的后验
责任还不错，很高兴告诉我什么是责任
right now we have observed the day time we have updated the posterior of Z so
the responsibility okay so nice to be on tells me what's the responsibility the
责任还不错，很高兴告诉我什么是责任
tells me what's the responsibility the component K takes to explain point n
组件K用来解释点n好的，以及您何时实际要
component K takes to explain point n okay and when you actually are going to
okay and when you actually are going to this responsibility every point you can
您可以根据此责任在每个点上放一点红色
this responsibility every point you can put a bit of red depending on this
put a bit of red depending on this posterior responsibilities then actually
后验责任然后实际上当您执行此图时，他们看起来
posterior responsibilities then actually when you do this graphs they look
when you do this graphs they look wonderful
很棒，在文学中，人们就是这样
wonderful and in the literature that's how people
and in the literature that's how people demonstrate the Costera supposed to be
演示一下如果您还可以的话，Costera应该是现在，但是这些是
demonstrate the Costera supposed to be now if you're back okay but these are
now if you're back okay but these are the post irresponsible
帖子不负责任，好，我们讨论这个问题时，
the post irresponsible okay and we have discussed this when we
okay and we have discussed this when we were talking about expectation
在谈论期望最大化时，我们进行了讲座和
were talking about expectation maximization we spent lectures and
maximization we spent lectures and lectures on this because this is
关于这方面的讲座，因为这是
Z和K的宝贵基本期望是我们的NK，您还记得，因为
maximization we spent lectures and lectures on this because this is
valuable basically expectation of Z and K is our NK you remember that because
Z和K的宝贵基本期望是我们的NK，您还记得，因为
K is our NK you remember that because you can only take values 0 and 1 right
您只能正确取值0和1，因此期望值等于
you can only take values 0 and 1 right so the expectation is equal to the
so the expectation is equal to the probability that's the posterior
这就是后验概率，即R和K直到现在
probability that's the posterior probability which is R and K now up to
probability which is R and K now up to now is right that we have a nice job for
现在是正确的，我们为此做得很好，但是此R的此设置取决于
now is right that we have a nice job for this but this setting for this R depends
this but this setting for this R depends on many expectations with respect to the
对其他分布有很多期望，所以请注意我们可以
on many expectations with respect to the other distributions so notice we can
other distributions so notice we can actually complete all of this we are
实际上完成了所有这些工作，我们要下班了，我的意思是很高兴地说
actually complete all of this we are going off work I mean it's nice to say
going off work I mean it's nice to say this is what it is but how do you
就是这样，但是您如何计算侧倾，所以我们将继续
this is what it is but how do you compute a roll and and so we will keep
compute a roll and and so we will keep going and see how about I think we have
去看看怎么样，当我们讨论关于
going and see how about I think we have seen them when we discuss about
seen them when we discuss about expectation maximization so this is the
期望最大化，所以这是垃圾中的要点，随身携带
expectation maximization so this is the point in the garbage and carry all right
point in the garbage and carry all right so basically whatever the points when
因此，基本上，无论您总结这个神秘的看跌期权的要点如何
so basically whatever the points when you sum this mysterious puts benefits
you sum this mysterious puts benefits now this is the effective sample name on
现在这是高斯K上的有效样本名称
now this is the effective sample name on the Gaussian K all right so you take on
the Gaussian K all right so you take on the exist you want to apply them with
您想将它们应用于后验可能性，这是
the exist you want to apply them with the posterior possibilities and this is
the posterior possibilities and this is the effective area okay so basically I
有效区域好吧，所以基本上我在定义这个，因为如果你有
the effective area okay so basically I am defining this because if you have
am defining this because if you have these definitions you will see that the
这些定义，您将看到代数将被简化，并且一个
these definitions you will see that the algebra is going to simplify and one
algebra is going to simplify and one identity that you may want to pay
您可能要注意的身份，因为这些条款不能
identity that you may want to pay attention because the terms can be not
attention because the terms can be not just on this setting but in many related
只是在此设置上，但在许多相关设置中将具有这些
just on this setting but in many related settings will have these
settings will have these responsibilities it is very nice
责任是一个很好的身份，基本上直接来自
responsibilities it is very nice identity that comes directly basically
identity that comes directly basically by taking the definition of SK and
通过采用SK的定义并将其扩展为可以
by taking the definition of SK and expanding it okay
expanding it okay so somewhere in the derivations we've
所以在推导中的某个地方，我们今天没有说过，但是当我们阅读
so somewhere in the derivations we've not said today but when we read the
not said today but when we read the notes
注意这是一个计算或概念，所以
notes this is a calculation or concept okay so
this is a calculation or concept okay so we want to calculate Q up by mu and
我们想通过mu和lambda来计算Q，所以这就是那个的爱
we want to calculate Q up by mu and lambda so this would be the love of that
lambda so this would be the love of that advocate pioneer lanta will be the
倡导者开拓者兰塔将是对原木Z的期望
advocate pioneer lanta will be the expectation with respect to Z of the log
expectation with respect to Z of the log of the join the likelihood with the only
我们唯一要保持的加入可能性是
of the join the likelihood with the only times we're going to be keeping is
times we're going to be keeping is anything that depends on P near Atlanta
在亚特兰大附近依赖P的任何东西，在那个时候
anything that depends on P near Atlanta and in those times anything that
and in those times anything that contains it will take expectations so
包含期望，所以基本上你会从中得到
contains it will take expectations so basically what you get is you get from
basically what you get is you get from the prior to get love of the prior from
从堆中获得先验的先验记得我们有一个联合
the prior to get love of the prior from the pile remember we had a joint
the pile remember we had a joint distribution of in Atlanta but Gaussian
在亚特兰大的分布，但高斯向导的分布有一个0取决于
distribution of in Atlanta but Gaussian wizard distribution there is a 0 depends
wizard distribution there is a 0 depends on PI so we can have an expectation this
在PI上，所以我们可以期望在此时间内有这个Z记住我们有
on PI so we can have an expectation this Z here inside the time remember we have
Z here inside the time remember we have the Gaussian to the powers east of the
信号以东的高斯下降了，所以我们有一个
the Gaussian to the powers east of the signal comes down so we have an
signal comes down so we have an expectation times the log of the
期望乘以高斯对数加上常数就可以了，
expectation times the log of the Gaussian plus constants okay and
Gaussian plus constants okay and interestingly enough right when you look
有趣的是，当您查看此分布时，就好了
interestingly enough right when you look at this distribution okay my thing just
at this distribution okay my thing just died okay alright so when you look on on
死了好吧，好吧，所以当你继续观察别人与你在一起时，
died okay alright so when you look on on the does anybody else with you that's a
the does anybody else with you that's a very stupid question right it's like
非常愚蠢的问题，就像问您是否有整个森林
very stupid question right it's like asking if you have any an entire forest
asking if you have any an entire forest walking right something like that okay
像这样走路就可以了，所以你没有电池怎么办
walking right something like that okay so you have no batteries how can you
so you have no batteries how can you leave home without batteries that's
没有电池就离开家，这是不可接受的
leave home without batteries that's unacceptable
unacceptable okay so you can circle the equation they
好吧，你可以圈出等式，它们是正确的，但肯定超过K的权利
okay so you can circle the equation they are right but the certainly over K right
are right but the certainly over K right because you can see the two summations
因为你可以看到凯利的两个总结，当你
because you can see the two summations from Kelly and we have no joy when you
from Kelly and we have no joy when you get rid of the log basically you get the
摆脱日志，基本上可以得到K的因式分解，所以29
get rid of the log basically you get the factorization over K so 29
factorization over K so 29 okay so so tsunamis I'm gonna put in the
好吧，所以我要把海啸放到
okay so so tsunamis I'm gonna put in the the probably shall we have the condition
the probably shall we have the condition of Z given pi we know expectations from
给定pi的Z的值，我们知道岗位不负责任的期望，因此
of Z given pi we know expectations from exists of the post irresponsibility so
exists of the post irresponsibility so we planned in all of this together all
我们一起计划了所有这一切
we planned in all of this together all right
right actually sometimes fathers have life if
实际上，有时候，如果多功能性强，父亲们就会有生命。
actually sometimes fathers have life if you versatility the okay this the bottom
还是我需要更改好的好的好的让我试试
or I need to change okay all right okay all right let me try
好，要比你想的要学习
okay have to learn than you think yeah
好吧，所以这个牛角包好吧，这个好
all right right so this croissant okay this good
right so this croissant okay this good oh I see okay oh this is heavy lighting
哦，我知道了，哦，这是沉重的照明，很好，它非常强大
oh I see okay oh this is heavy lighting nice this is extra powerful it comes
nice this is extra powerful it comes from Beijing you know when planes fly
来自北京，您知道飞机何时飞行，就在天空上飞，让我使用
from Beijing you know when planes fly you go up on the skies right let me use
you go up on the skies right let me use it outside the classroom okay
它在教室外面好吧，它非常强大，我会
it outside the classroom okay all right it's very powerful I will
all right it's very powerful I will confiscate it right this here this is
没收这是这里，这是我们得到的，我们需要替代精通
confiscate it right this here this is what we get we need to substitute versed
what we get we need to substitute versed in there all right
在那里，实际上是期望，让我们看看
in there all right actually the expectations and let's see
actually the expectations and let's see okay let's see what we get
好吧，让我们再看看我们会怎样，我不想给你们所有人
okay let's see what we get okay again I don't want to give you all
okay again I don't want to give you all the algebra but there are some tricky
代数，但总有一些棘手的事情
the algebra but there are some tricky things that come all the time
things that come all the time so if I notice them I need to tell you
所以如果我注意到他们，我需要告诉你发生了什么，所以基本上我们开始
so if I notice them I need to tell you what's going on so basically we start
what's going on so basically we start killed in this expectation of respect to
在对零的期望中被杀死，可能性还可以，并且
killed in this expectation of respect to zero the joint of likelihood okay and
以某种精确度进行超额结余决策，然后以某种方式带来
over carry as decisions with some precision that then comes with some way
precision that then comes with some way start so you don't have to take the one
开始，所以您不必进行一项服务，您可能会说平常的话
start so you don't have to take the one service and you may say well the usual
service and you may say well the usual distribution of a distribution or posted
分布或发布确定矩阵的分布，是的，您必须
distribution of a distribution or posted definite matrices well yeah you have to
definite matrices well yeah you have to do it because of this character right
因为这个角色正确而要做，所以你必须这样做，这样你就可以做到
do it because of this character right you have to do this so you take most
you have to do this so you take most launched etc etc and and you get
推出等等等等，基本上您会看到
launched etc etc and and you get basically you look at the terms that
basically you look at the terms that they were warning me
他们警告我兰塔，他看着最佳
they were warning me Lanta and he looked at the optimal
Lanta and he looked at the optimal distribution so out of this you can
分布，因此您可以提取伦敦的音素，您可以看到
distribution so out of this you can extract phoneme in London you can see
extract phoneme in London you can see lower to start up in Atlanta is
较低的亚特兰大开始基本上是这两条线好了
lower to start up in Atlanta is basically this two lines here alright
令人惊讶的好吧，所以这是
surprising okay alright so this is the
好吧，例如好吧，如果你用这个表达式
okay for example okay and if you with in this expression
okay and if you with in this expression you basically get a Gaussian in new all
您基本上会得到一个新的高斯函数，如果您将它放在
you basically get a Gaussian in new all right you can see it if you place the
right you can see it if you place the square and that's the mastership
广场，那是大师的权利，所以如果您和
square and that's the mastership alright so from this again if you and
alright so from this again if you and now how do you defend the posterior is
现在，你如何捍卫后方是有条件的几次
now how do you defend the posterior is the conditional for several times the
the conditional for several times the variation distribution of Ishita so if
石田的变化分布，所以如果您采取行动，您实际上可以
variation distribution of Ishita so if you take an action that you can actually
you take an action that you can actually compute the I'll keep going backwards if
计算一下，如果您采用可以的功能，我将继续往前走
compute the I'll keep going backwards if you take the function that you can
you take the function that you can actually compute the approximation of
实际计算lambda的后验的近似值，所以如果您这样做
actually compute the approximation of the posterior of lambda and so if you do
the posterior of lambda and so if you do the algebra you get many different weird
代数，您会得到许多不同的怪异术语，如果您有耐心，并且
the algebra you get many different weird terms okay and if you have patience and
terms okay and if you have patience and you actually homophobe has disappear all
你实际上同性恋已经消失了所有的东西抵消了，你得到他们的
you actually homophobe has disappear all the things cancel out and you get their
the things cancel out and you get their wonderful approximation for the love of
对lambda k键的热爱，这是一个奇妙的近似值
wonderful approximation for the love of the key of lambda k that looks like that
the key of lambda k that looks like that okay well this wk inversed comes to be
好吧，这周倒过来就是这个，你可能会认为这是一个
okay well this wk inversed comes to be this which you may think it's a
this which you may think it's a complicated expression okay and UK comes
复杂的表达式好了，英国变成u 0加10 K，你知道我
complicated expression okay and UK comes to be u 0 plus 10 K and you know that I
to be u 0 plus 10 K and you know that I prefer this is the relative distribution
偏爱这是相对分布效应，所以当你看这个权利的时候
prefer this is the relative distribution effect so when you look at this right
effect so when you look at this right you can still submit additional under K
您仍然可以在K下提交其他内容，但这是什么类型的分布
you can still submit additional under K but what type of distribution is this
but what type of distribution is this exponential you think I get so what you
您认为我得到了指数，所以您得到了向导分发，这是
exponential you think I get so what you gets a wizard distribution and here's
gets a wizard distribution and here's the answer okay alright so the combined
答案很好，所以组合的基本分布公式兰塔是
the answer okay alright so the combined basically distribution formula lanta is
basically distribution formula lanta is a Gaussian wizard okay so the Gaussian
高斯向导还可以，因此高斯精度lambda随带
a Gaussian wizard okay so the Gaussian the precision lambda comes with the
the precision lambda comes with the wizard next to it and kill all the
向导旁边，并有选择地杀死所有参数
wizard next to it and kill all the parameters selectively the approximation
parameters selectively the approximation to the posterior of new claim of decay
到新的衰变要求的后部，与我们之前的先验是相同的12
to the posterior of new claim of decay it is the same 12 as the priors that we
it is the same 12 as the priors that we use from your lambda
使用lambda的唯一区别是参数
use from your lambda the only differences the parameters
the only differences the parameters because 0 and mu 0 etc or nu 0 w0 have
因为0和mu 0 etc或nu 0 w0现在已经更新，所以有
because 0 and mu 0 etc or nu 0 w0 have been updated now and this have sort of
been updated now and this have sort of the updates of the parameters so
参数的更新，因此基本上使用共轭先验给出了
the updates of the parameters so basically using conjugate priors gave a
basically using conjugate priors gave a similar variation approximation that is
相似的变化近似值，对于所有相同的事物来说都是相同的，所以这
similar variation approximation that is the same identical for all right so this
the same identical for all right so this is very nice
是非常好的
好的，好的，我们将继续返回报告，好的
the same identical for all right so this is very nice
okay and all right so we're gonna keep going back reports again all right so
好的，好的，我们将继续返回报告，好的
going back reports again all right so tell me is the conversation here
告诉我这里是对话，我们需要回到另一个问题
tell me is the conversation here we need to go back to another question
we need to go back to another question over the responsibilities and I'm gonna
在责任上，我要把所有这些东西都说出来
over the responsibilities and I'm gonna put all of these things up so to say
put all of these things up so to say that the relationship immediately
那个关系马上就代数了，所以记住这个
that the relationship immediately algebra so remember the of this
algebra so remember the of this responsibilities this out we are
我们从文明要求中规范了我们的责任
responsibilities this out we are normalized us from civilities requires
normalized us from civilities requires the expectation of the log of I claim
我要求的对数的期望值要求对
the expectation of the log of I claim requires the expectation of the line of
requires the expectation of the line of this matrices lambda K and the
这个矩阵lambda K和对我的期望
this matrices lambda K and the expectation with respect to me along to
expectation with respect to me along to exist okay so you know what you need to
存在，所以你知道你需要教我们做这个代数的事情，所以
exist okay so you know what you need to have taught us to do this algebra so
have taught us to do this algebra so let's complete this you need the
让我们完成这一点，您需要对我亚特兰大的期望尊重
let's complete this you need the expectation respect to me Atlanta which
expectation respect to me Atlanta which is fundamental basically do every time
是基本的，基本上每次您看到此表格时，
is fundamental basically do every time you see this form and you have an
you see this form and you have an expectation I have written this as the
期望我把它写成lambda时代xx转置的教区
expectation I have written this as the parish of lambda times xx transpose
parish of lambda times xx transpose have you seen that before it's a
您是否看到过，在将其作为基本知识之前，无处不在
have you seen that before it's a fundamental take basic and everywhere
fundamental take basic and everywhere when you get this you write it when you
当你得到这个你写它，当你有X转置lambda乘以X你我
when you get this you write it when you have X transpose lambda times X you I
have X transpose lambda times X you I this as the trace of lambda X X
这作为lambda XX的痕迹转置好了，然后我们需要
this as the trace of lambda X X transpose okay and then we need
transpose okay and then we need expectation with the posterior of
期望与黑色素的后部，我们使用变分
expectation with the posterior of mylanta we use the variational
mylanta we use the variational approximation of those so we're gonna
这些近似，所以我们首先要进行整合McCadden和
approximation of those so we're gonna first an integration McCadden an
first an integration McCadden an integration in you need this you need to
在您需要的集成中，您需要了解以下方法的含义
integration in you need this you need to know the mean of the ways of
know the mean of the ways of distribution to do that so this
分布来做到这一点，基本上，如果您使用
distribution to do that so this basically if you use the properties of
basically if you use the properties of the wizard distribution are no problem
向导的分发是没有问题的，仍然需要我们对此进行计算
the wizard distribution are no problem and it remains we need to calculate this
and it remains we need to calculate this expectation of the lava pie PA all right
熔岩派PA的期望好吧，好吧，你可以，我不会
expectation of the lava pie PA all right okay so all right you can I am NOT going
okay so all right you can I am NOT going to elaborate on this okay for this if
如果您在Wikipedia上学习声明了此内容，则可以对此进行详细说明
to elaborate on this okay for this if you study in Wikipedia the declared this
you study in Wikipedia the declared this tradition this expectation of a lot of
传统上对大量Pi粘土的这种期望基本上是身体
tradition this expectation of a lot of Pi clay comes to be basically the body
Pi clay comes to be basically the body gamma function computed on alpha t minus
在alpha t上计算的伽马函数减去超声医师的情况，这是通过
gamma function computed on alpha t minus the sonographer case this is the by
the sonographer case this is the by gamma function and and then we have to
伽玛功能，然后我们必须完成这一痛苦准备，但您永远不会
gamma function and and then we have to complete this pain prepare but you never
complete this pain prepare but you never satanic or in any machine landing book
撒旦或任何机器着陆书中实际上都记得他有这个
satanic or in any machine landing book actually remember he has this
actually remember he has this calculations explicitly but you will
明确地进行计算，但是您永远不会讨论如何
calculations explicitly but you will never take a discussion of how you
never take a discussion of how you compute the expectation with respect to
计算关于爱的分配方式的期望
compute the expectation with respect to ways of distribution of the love of the
ways of distribution of the love of the determinant of a wizard distribution all
向导分布的决定因素好吧，所以我们认为
determinant of a wizard distribution all right okay so so there is we are think
right okay so so there is we are think okay and I am NOT going to am I going
好吧，我不会去，我会倒退，是的，所以这是
okay and I am NOT going to am I going backwards yeah no okay so so this is
backwards yeah no okay so so this is what we need we need to calculate the
我们需要什么，我们需要计算此lovicott行列式的期望
what we need we need to calculate the expectation of this lovicott determinant
expectation of this lovicott determinant by the Council of the Gaussian with
由高斯理事会就此平衡添加
by the Council of the Gaussian with respect to this the balanced addition of
respect to this the balanced addition of lambda which the wizard okay and I
lambda，向导还可以，我记得我第一次打开它时知道
lambda which the wizard okay and I remember when I first open this you know
remember when I first open this you know three years ago you know the miracles of
三年前，您知道了Google的奇迹，好吧，我遇到了一个参考
three years ago you know the miracles of Google okay I came across a reference
Google okay I came across a reference but basically you can approximate this
但基本上您可以将其近似为美容方分布的总和
but basically you can approximate this as a sum of beauty square distributions
as a sum of beauty square distributions and with some trivial answer actually
并在这张幻灯片上给出了一些琐碎的答案，实际上我不是
and with some trivial answer actually which is on this slide that I'm not
which is on this slide that I'm not going to elaborate you can actually
要详细说明，您实际上可以分析地计算出
going to elaborate you can actually compute analytically the expectation of
compute analytically the expectation of value
珍视兰卡的决定因素，这就是
value the determinant of Lanka and this is the
the determinant of Lanka and this is the expression well again this is the by
再次很好地表达，这显然是伽玛分布
expression well again this is the by gamma distribution obviously here my
gamma distribution obviously here my parentheses should be inside the
括号应该放在参数中，这样他们会想念它的
parentheses should be inside the argument they're gonna miss it so
argument they're gonna miss it so everything on this okay can be
可以的一切都可以计算出来，我会给你一个
everything on this okay can be calculated and I'm going to give you a
calculated and I'm going to give you a very compact oh and the very compact
非常紧凑哦，非常紧凑的一点是您在底部看到的好吗
very compact oh and the very compact point is what you see on the bottom okay
point is what you see on the bottom okay so this involves this cherry pie which
所以这涉及到这个樱桃派，我们在这里将其定义为指数
so this involves this cherry pie which we define it here to be the exponential
we define it here to be the exponential of this expectation this charaluta that
这个期望的charaluta，我们定义为这个指数
of this expectation this charaluta that we define to be the exponential of this
we define to be the exponential of this expectation and then this term inside
期望，然后我们是日经里面的这个术语是mu 0 plus n K好吧
expectation and then this term inside we're Nikkei is mu 0 plus n K all right
we're Nikkei is mu 0 plus n K all right which are this idea so basically I can
基本上，这是我的主意，因此我可以找到这行的摘要
which are this idea so basically I can find this line that is a summary of
find this line that is a summary of everything this is you can program it in
这就是一切，您可以在几分钟内对其进行编程，好吧，有人
everything this is you can program it in in a few minutes okay right somebody
in a few minutes okay right somebody gives you we actually passed any of this
给你，我们实际上通过了这个结果，我现在就知道了
gives you we actually passed any of this result I would know okay now this is
result I would know okay now this is written as an easter time step because
由于与预期的相似之处，被写为复活节时间的步骤
written as an easter time step because of the similarities with the expectation
of the similarities with the expectation maximization so in the easter you have
最大化，所以在复活节，你已经成为一个基本的责任
maximization so in the easter you have become a basically the responsibilities
become a basically the responsibilities and to give make the responsibilities
并承担责任，您需要这些期望
and to give make the responsibilities you need these expectations this cherry
you need these expectations this cherry pie and the can be lambda K and this is
派和可以是lambda K，这就是这些职责的公式
pie and the can be lambda K and this is the formula for these responsibilities
the formula for these responsibilities whereas we have the responsibilities we
而我们有责任，可以带m步来计算
whereas we have the responsibilities we can bring the m-step calculate the
can bring the m-step calculate the attractive number of points on its
高斯点上具有吸引力的点数带有有效平均值
attractive number of points on its Gaussian carry the effective mean values
Gaussian carry the effective mean values and variance and update all the
和方差并更新所有参数，然后继续迭代
and variance and update all the parameters and then you keep iterating
parameters and then you keep iterating and human converts okay you win converts
和人类convert依好吧，你赢了s依
就像我之前提到的，这种压缩方式已经扩展到
parameters and then you keep iterating and human converts okay you win converts
and again as I mentioned this compressions have been extended to
就像我之前提到的，这种压缩方式已经扩展到
compressions have been extended to anything he makes Raghava processes and
他制作Raghava流程和变化的任何内容也扩展到了
anything he makes Raghava processes and variation have been extended also to an
variation have been extended also to an infinite in thousand distributions and
无限的一千个分布，交替地混合了高斯
infinite in thousand distributions and alternately makes mixture of Gaussian
alternately makes mixture of Gaussian processes okay
可以处理一个例子，是Python代码，可以
processes okay an example is a Python code okay I'm
an example is a Python code okay I'm gonna pass this right actually on this
实际上会在这张幻灯片上传递一些正确的方程式，但我不是
gonna pass this right actually on this slide some of the equations but I'm not
slide some of the equations but I'm not gonna show you today they somehow don't
今天要给你看，因为它们被键入，它们以某种方式表现不佳
gonna show you today they somehow don't show very well because they were typed
show very well because they were typed on there on a Mac so they I need to sort
在Mac上，所以他们需要重温一些问题，但是
on there on a Mac so they I need to sort of revive some of their questions but
of revive some of their questions but you know we will fix it today so
你知道我们今天会修复它，所以希望是谁
you know we will fix it today so hopefully so who's that so an example
hopefully so who's that so an example that has an issue of 6,000 so these are
的问题是6,000，所以这些是我的数据点和椭圆
that has an issue of 6,000 so these are my data points and the ellipses that you
my data points and the ellipses that you will see is basically one side of the
将会看到基本上是国家密度控制的一侧
will see is basically one side of the nation density controls each of the
nation density controls each of the parents I caused that has already
我造成的父母已经没事了
parents I caused that has already alright that inside it's eclipse that
alright that inside it's eclipse that corresponds to the main content of the
对应于混合方程式的主要内容，这是您开始的时间
corresponds to the main content of the mix equation and this is when you start
mix equation and this is when you start alright so these are the prior makes
好了，所以这些是先前的制造分区，但随着我们的进行，我们将继续
alright so these are the prior makes partitions but as we we will continue
partitions but as we we will continue this this will be the color will be
这将是颜色，将基于后继职责
this this will be the color will be based on the posterior responsibilities
based on the posterior responsibilities so this is this is not okay this is
所以这是不好的，这是迭代15好的，这是
so this is this is not okay this is iteration 15 okay on this are the
iteration 15 okay on this are the different Gaussian basically but you
基本上是不同的高斯，但是您计算这种情况60
different Gaussian basically but you compute this situation 60 and this
compute this situation 60 and this situation 120 so basically the model
情况120，所以从2000年开始模型基本上崩溃了，现在您知道了
situation 120 so basically the model collapse from 2000 now you know what
collapse from 2000 now you know what happened you know you say I have a
碰巧你知道你说我混了
happened you know you say I have a mixture
mixture collapse on on two gaussians well yeah
对两个高斯人崩溃了，是的，因为我们使用过的这个球员
collapse on on two gaussians well yeah because this players that we have used
because this players that we have used for you know they enforce with the
因为您知道他们会用流行词强制执行，所以
for you know they enforce with the buzzword supposed to do okay so the
buzzword supposed to do okay so the spires we use basically kills some of
我们使用的尖刺基本上可以杀死某些组件
spires we use basically kills some of the components okay
the components okay and the misny that's why he gives the
这就是为什么他对乳脂这个名字也给出了相同的想法的原因
and the misny that's why he gives the same ideas right for the name cream
same ideas right for the name cream actually remember I have and into a
真的记得我有一个混在一起，所以你说一百你好1200
actually remember I have and into a mixed so you say hundred you well 1200
mixed so you say hundred you well 1200 would go down to five ten you know so
会下降到五点十，你知道，所以在没有你的情况下会下降到120
would go down to five ten you know so here it goes down to to 120 without you
here it goes down to to 120 without you having to do so the city is Islam sort
必须这样做，这座城市是伊斯兰教，而不是以某种暴力的方式说
having to do so the city is Islam sort of not in in a sort of violent way say
of not in in a sort of violent way say use two components it's mostly the two
使用两个组件，主要是两个组件都不会出现，因为
use two components it's mostly the two components are not coming because the
components are not coming because the responsibilities taken for the data
数据点承担的责任基本上为零
responsibilities taken for the data points are basically zero alright
points are basically zero alright there's zero these block okay this is
这些块为零，好吧，这是
再一次幸存下来，您可以描述一下
points are basically zero alright there's zero these block okay this is
and again alright survives you to describe look at
再一次幸存下来，您可以描述一下
alright survives you to describe look at this code right thing works okay so
这段代码正确的事情很好，所以
组件幸免于难，它花费了九十年代的大部分时间
alright survives you to describe look at this code right thing works okay so
component survived all right and it takes so much of it relations ninety
组件幸免于难，它花费了九十年代的大部分时间
takes so much of it relations ninety iterations you notice this is the an in
迭代，您会注意到这是一个相反的单调增加
iterations you notice this is the an in opposite monotonically increases okay
opposite monotonically increases okay and this is this would work here
这是这将在这里工作
所以这一次，如果您知道这种不同，基本上我认为这是
opposite monotonically increases okay and this is this would work here
so this time if you know of this different basically I supposed this
所以这一次，如果您知道这种不同，基本上我认为这是
different basically I supposed this isn't the postilion values of alpha
不是alpha电锯的postilion值
isn't the postilion values of alpha chainsaw
chainsaw okay the Brazilian values of alpha K and
好吧，alpha K的巴西值，您注意到最终您知道
okay the Brazilian values of alpha K and you notice eventually you know after
you notice eventually you know after interation 94 so this is some
交互94，所以这是之后的一些中间响应迭代
interation 94 so this is some intermediate response iteration after
intermediate response iteration after iteration 912 only 2000 volunteers
912次迭代只有2000名志愿者幸存下来，所以这实际上可能是
iteration 912 only 2000 volunteers survived okay so this actually may be
survived okay so this actually may be the same data set as the one I saw you
与我在几秒钟内用Python代码看到的数据集相同的数据集
the same data set as the one I saw you with the Python code just a few seconds
with the Python code just a few seconds ago
前
不想说什么好
with the Python code just a few seconds ago
don't want to say anything about okay
让我看看还有什么我知道我需要告诉你的地方
let me see what else I know where what I need to tell you
need to tell you so we need to you may ask me since you
所以我们需要您可能会问我，因为您对此非常兴奋，您可能会说
so we need to you may ask me since you got very excited with this you may say
got very excited with this you may say an evaluation all right who is the
评估好吗谁是分布有任何希望下降
an evaluation all right who is the distribution is there any hope drops
distribution is there any hope drops recompute any of them telling me I've no
重新计算任何一个告诉我，我没有示例幻灯片47，因为显然
recompute any of them telling me I've no example slide 47 because obviously
example slide 47 because obviously what's the perfect ultra-light would say
完美的超轻型飞机在这里要说的是数据如何适应您所知道的
what's the perfect ultra-light would say here is how the data fit you know in so
here is how the data fit you know in so many components where I'm interested to
我想知道的许多组件实际上可以计算出
many components where I'm interested to know is can actually compute the
know is can actually compute the posterior of a new data point okay so
一个新数据点的后验，所以这个方程式就是后验
posterior of a new data point okay so this equation so this is the posterior
this equation so this is the posterior distribution tell me exactly everything
分布告诉我您在等式上看到的所有信息异丙基
distribution tell me exactly everything you see on this equation isopropyl
you see on this equation isopropyl integrates information on Z so tell me
整合了Z上的信息，所以请告诉我他们到底发生了什么
integrates information on Z so tell me exactly what's going on their
exactly what's going on their distribution
分配
什么是预测分布
exactly what's going on their distribution
what's the predictive distribution
参数，长度和变量，所以这些是正确的参数，这
parameters and length and variables so these are the parameters right and this
these are the parameters right and this C heart is the latent variable
换句话说，C心是与X心对应的潜在变量
C heart is the latent variable corresponding to X heart in other words
corresponding to X heart in other words if I knew that that component you know
如果我知道该成分，您会抱怨混合的产生
if I knew that that component you know complain to the mixture of generates the
complain to the mixture of generates the point X 1/2 all right this would be the
X 1/2点好吧，这就是可能性或不正确，这就是我们
point X 1/2 all right this would be the likelihood or not right that's what we
likelihood or not right that's what we must be an integration on all the
必须是所有未知数（包括Z bar）的积分，我选择
must be an integration on all the unknowns including Z bar and I picked as
unknowns including Z bar and I picked as a summation because the bar takes what
求和，因为条取的是它的值，这是一个，这是一个
a summation because the bar takes what values it's a it's a it's a
values it's a it's a it's a you know so so I'm going it said this
你知道，所以我要说的是这个国家，我要选择
you know so so I'm going it said this country which I'm going to pick the
country which I'm going to pick the Grantham Z alright okay okay
Grantham Z好吧好吧好吧
由该版本生成，下一个系数为K，它将变为
country which I'm going to pick the Grantham Z alright okay okay
generated by this version the next coefficient by K and this will become
由该版本生成，下一个系数为K，它将变为
coefficient by K and this will become this Gaussian and obviously this mistake
这个高斯，显然这个错误是非常复杂的，所以我们要
this Gaussian and obviously this mistake is very complicated so we're going to
is very complicated so we're going to approximate it with a variational
用变分分布来近似它，所以Q PI Q mu K lambda K so
approximate it with a variational distribution so Q PI Q mu K lambda K so
distribution so Q PI Q mu K lambda K so this the distribution we welcome this
这个分布，我们欢迎这个记住，我们得到了这种限制
this the distribution we welcome this remember we got this restrictor izing of
remember we got this restrictor izing of Delta and Kelly and this came to be
Delta和Kelly，这成为千人向导K的优化
Delta and Kelly and this came to be optimization of the K of thousand wizard
optimization of the K of thousand wizard distributions okay
发行版还可以，当然他们现在正在尝试什么
distributions okay and of course what they are now trying
and of course what they are now trying to perform this integration right now
立即执行此集成，这意味着您永远不会放弃正确的选择
to perform this integration right now what that means you never give up right
what that means you never give up right because if the least a closed-form
因为如果至少有一个封闭形式的解决方案，然后您走了，您现在说我的
because if the least a closed-form solution and you go and you say now my
solution and you go and you say now my references computer program to do this
引用计算机程序做这个的人会笑的就像你
references computer program to do this people would be laughing is like you
people would be laughing is like you must be kidding you know when we read
一定是在开玩笑，您知道我们读这本书的开始时间，因为有一个
must be kidding you know when we read the book starts because there is a
the book starts because there is a mythical solution this can you guess I
神话般的解决方案，您能猜到我的意思是，在我向您展示任何内容之前，您可以
mythical solution this can you guess I mean before I show you anything can you
mean before I show you anything can you guess you know it's just from your birth
猜猜你知道这只是从你的出生时间尺度来看是什么类型的分布
guess you know it's just from your birth time scale what type of distribution
time scale what type of distribution this may come to be I mean just yes so
这可能是我的意思是，是的，所以我们再次浏览了一个唯一的广告位
this may come to be I mean just yes so again we have a browse unique slots
again we have a browse unique slots heart rate right okay components and now
心率正确，好组件，现在我们尝试从您身上产生X，您知道
heart rate right okay components and now we try to produce from you X you know
we try to produce from you X you know what's the probability what do you think
您认为发生什么事情的几率是多少，我的意思是给您
what's the probability what do you think is going to happen I mean just give you
is going to happen I mean just give you some choices
有些选择让我解释一下，所以水平只是
some choices let me account so the level is just
let me account so the level is just again it collapse to some mixed of some
再次崩溃到一些大写的K成分混合在一起，那么
again it collapse to some mixed of some capital K components so what will the
capital K components so what will the predictive distribution look like at the
预测性分布看起来就像一天结束时一样
predictive distribution look like at the end of the day
无论如何，我并不感到惊讶
I'm not surprised you know anyways
良好的纪律通过它唱给你，成为高斯人的混合体
well discipline is sing to you through it becomes to the mix of gaussians
高斯混合体不，我的意思是不会让我惊讶
mixture of gaussians no I mean it will not surprise me
not surprise me and that's how it doesn't come to be a
除非你有一个高斯主义者，否则这就是为什么不成为高斯部长的原因
and that's how it doesn't come to be a minister of gaussians unless you have a
minister of gaussians unless you have a lots of data but it goes to the next
很多数据，但是到什么分布的下三分之一
lots of data but it goes to the next third of what distribution what what is
third of what distribution what what is very close to browse it didn't take this
非常接近浏览，这没什么问题，因此成为一种混合
very close to browse it didn't take this to be a okay so it comes to be a mixture
to be a okay so it comes to be a mixture of didn t distributions and only on the
没有分布，仅在您的限制下，只有大量数据，因此
of didn t distributions and only on the limit of you only have a lots of data so
limit of you only have a lots of data so the prior effects basically disappear
先前的影响基本上消失了，这个qt-变成高斯了，还好
the prior effects basically disappear this qt- becomes a Gaussian it and okay
答案栏实际上并不像我让它看起来正确时那样痛苦
the answer bar is actually it's not as painful as I make it to look like right
painful as I make it to look like right so you will you need basically the
所以您基本上需要该系数YK的期望值
so you will you need basically the expectations of this coefficients YK
expectations of this coefficients YK coming from the declare distribution you
来自于声明分布，您将基本上需要使用它
coming from the declare distribution you will need basically to work with this
will need basically to work with this okay and so you can see actually we know
好的，所以您可以看到实际上我们知道预测性的
okay and so you can see actually we know it comes that the predictive
it comes that the predictive distribution is an integration of the
分布是对每个K lambda K的lambda的积分
distribution is an integration of the lambda of the for each K lambda K over
lambda of the for each K lambda K over diffusion okay but we precision that you
扩散还可以，但是我们很精确，您在这里看到的是向导分布
diffusion okay but we precision that you see here that's a wizard distribution
see here that's a wizard distribution okay so again it is an integration of
好的，这又是高斯人的亚特兰大与巫师的融合
okay so again it is an integration of Atlanta of gaussians with Wizards you
Atlanta of gaussians with Wizards you know actually mattresses and actually I
知道实际上是床垫，实际上我应该给你这是一项家庭作业
know actually mattresses and actually I should have given you this is a homework
should have given you this is a homework right in an ideal environment because
就在理想的环境中，因为即使在主教那里也看到它有一个
right in an ideal environment because seeing even in bishops book it it has a
seeing even in bishops book it it has a little example that
您知道什么时候提示减少的小例子
little example that you know when the hint reduces for
you know when the hint reduces for remember we all like chapter 2
记得大家都喜欢第2章介绍学生的t分布
remember we all like chapter 2 introduces the student t distribution
introduces the student t distribution you know how he introduces it as a
您知道他是如何将其作为高斯混合的精确度引入的
you know how he introduces it as a mixture of gaussians for the precision
mixture of gaussians for the precision in the mixture so that components in the
在混合物中，这样混合物中的成分就是γ
in the mixture so that components in the mixture of what they are gamma
mixture of what they are gamma distributions
分布，所以实际上您显然可以在这里看到
distributions so actually obviously you can see here
so actually obviously you can see here if you have a multivariate Gaussian
如果您拥有多元高斯权，并且为此
if you have a multivariate Gaussian right and you take for this for this
right and you take for this for this precision a wizard you know you will get
精确的向导，您知道您将获得学生T分布的多元变量
precision a wizard you know you will get a student T distribution a multivariate
a student T distribution a multivariate unity distribution okay if you don't
统一分配好吧，如果你不相信我，请看第二章
unity distribution okay if you don't believe me look on chapter 2 where she
believe me look on chapter 2 where she introduces a student P you know with
介绍您认识的一个学生P
introduces a student P you know with sort of this construct that in one
sort of this construct that in one dimension I think so basically here
维度，我认为基本上在这里，我们将拥有完全相同的东西
dimension I think so basically here we'll we have this exact the same thing
we'll we have this exact the same thing we you know student eat some trivial
我们知道学生会吃一些琐碎的代数，基本上是看多少
we you know student eat some trivial algebra basically looking on how much
algebra basically looking on how much the distribution looks like
分布看起来像
好吧，好吧，今天的会员来自展示后部，我们写道
algebra basically looking on how much the distribution looks like
okay okay the membership today comes from the display posterior and we write
好吧，好吧，今天的会员来自展示后部，我们写道
from the display posterior and we write the coefficients in the Dirac
狄拉克分布中的系数我乘以
the coefficients in the Dirac distribution I have times the sum of
distribution I have times the sum of application so these are the mixture
应用程序，所以这些是混合成分，然后我有学生T
application so these are the mixture components and then I have the student T
components and then I have the student T with a precision basically that is given
基本上由该公式和您的炸弹给出的精度
with a precision basically that is given by this formula and the bomb in your
by this formula and the bomb in your case we had completed them before from
如果我们之前已经通过这些实验室和向导分发完成了它们
case we had completed them before from these labs and wizard distribution okay
these labs and wizard distribution okay so very nice formula okay all right I
很好的公式，好吧，我不知道为什么这么消极地讲好吧，所以
so very nice formula okay all right I don't know why so negative put okay so
don't know why so negative put okay so this is it's an approximation obviously
这显然是预测的近似值
this is it's an approximation obviously of the predicted
of the predicted tribution it's an approximation because
贡献，这是一个近似值，因为我们使用的参数百分比为
tribution it's an approximation because the percent of the parameters we use was
the percent of the parameters we use was not the exact posterior it was the
不是确切的后验，而是变化近似，所以这些
not the exact posterior it was the variation approximation okay so these
variation approximation okay so these exercises in in the notes so you're
在笔记中进行练习，以便您对可以执行的操作感兴趣，并且
exercises in in the notes so you're interested what you can do this and
interested what you can do this and again it's a very nice exercise if you
再次，这是一个非常好的练习，如果你看一下这个公式，让我
again it's a very nice exercise if you look at this formula and take let me
look at this formula and take let me look at the other parameters what
看一下其他参数，当我有很多数据时会发生什么
look at the other parameters what happens when I have a lots of data so
happens when I have a lots of data so when you take have to go to infinity or
当您必须去无穷大或者我通常有很多数据时，您可以
when you take have to go to infinity or I usually have a lots of data you can
I usually have a lots of data you can say with some trivial calculations
通过一些琐碎的计算，基本上可以得出这种预测后验
say with some trivial calculations basically that this predicting posterior
basically that this predicting posterior distribution comes to be a mixture of
发行将混合多种选择，您可能会有一些选择
distribution comes to be a mixture of options okay and you could have some
options okay and you could have some even have just this officer alright
甚至只请这个军官好吧，因为您知道您是否有要
even have just this officer alright because you know if you have a list to
because you know if you have a list to data to get all the powers forget
拥有全部权力的数据会忘记所有您知道的事情，然后再思考
data to get all the powers forget everything you know what then you think
everything you know what then you think so every dollar cell is defined by the
所以每个美元单元格都由积分的平均值来定义，例如当我们玩游戏时
so every dollar cell is defined by the averages of the points like when we play
averages of the points like when we play Nia that belongs to the Gaussian with
属于高斯的Nia具有这种协方差，然后基本上
Nia that belongs to the Gaussian with this covariance okay and then basically
this covariance okay and then basically the mixing questions is the persons
混合的问题是那些具有该组成部分的人
the mixing questions is the persons having that component there's the total
having that component there's the total number of points okay I mean you know
点数好吧，我的意思是你知道你可以知道你是否可以
number of points okay I mean you know you could have you know if you can its
you could have you know if you can its money to predict what's to know this
钱来预测这个答案是什么，这是他们承诺的价格
money to predict what's to know this answer this is a price they did promise
answer this is a price they did promise me if you try to do the answer block and
我，如果您尝试做答案块，那么您会得到一些水，当您
me if you try to do the answer block and then you get some water and when you
then you get some water and when you have a lots of vapor you don't bother to
有很多蒸气，您不用理会，这在其他方面是正确的，是吗
have a lots of vapor you don't bother to say is this correct in other ways is it
say is this correct in other ways is it going to give me a bit if it is not
如果不会给你一点你知道的话，我会给我一点
going to give me a bit if it is not going to give you that you know
going to give you that you know something is very wrong with the algebra
代数还好，所以在这种情况下
something is very wrong with the algebra okay so in this case when you take the
okay so in this case when you take the limit to lots of data the algebra comes
限制大量数据代数变得正确以执行此限制
limit to lots of data the algebra comes to be correct to do this limit you have
to be correct to do this limit you have and I
我知道你鼓励你尝试我的意思是不
and I you know encourage you to try I mean no
you know encourage you to try I mean no everything's in the nose at least pull
一切都在鼻子上，至少拉一下，然后变得头晕好吧，所以如果你
everything's in the nose at least pull it and then get dizzy okay so if you
it and then get dizzy okay so if you follow the algebra you have to use nice
跟随代数，您必须使用很好的近似值，您知道我能看到
follow the algebra you have to use nice approximations you know I can see
approximations you know I can see because there's run of actions you have
因为你有很多动作，史蒂夫（Steve）认为近似公式
because there's run of actions you have you Steve thinks approximation formula
you Steve thinks approximation formula and approximation kolento paste it
和近似kolento粘贴，它基本上包括所有后验
and approximation kolento paste it consists of basically all the posterior
consists of basically all the posterior distribution because you are the limit
分布，因为您是许多数据的限制，成为Delta函数，并且
distribution because you are the limit of many data become Delta functions and
of many data become Delta functions and at the end of the day without the
在一天结束时，如果没有该功能，就可以了
at the end of the day without the function you get right up okay
function you get right up okay all right I don't really have any
好吧，我真的没有时间，所以我们可能会告诉你我们需要
all right I don't really have any minutes so we might tell you we need to
minutes so we might tell you we need to do we need to go back whistling was it
我们需要回口哨吗16谢谢继续，您可以一概而论
do we need to go back whistling was it 16 thank you continue you can generalize
16 thank you continue you can generalize this and okay okay
这个，好吧好吧
因为比率和喜欢度实际上可以将其归纳为许多
16 thank you continue you can generalize this and okay okay
because rate and the likes you can actually generalize this for many many
因为比率和喜欢度实际上可以将其归纳为许多
actually generalize this for many many problems for situations where the joint
联合情感Z或我来自于
problems for situations where the joint affection Z or I come from the
affection Z or I come from the exponential problem okay and I think
指数问题好吧，我认为这是很多分布，无论在哪里
exponential problem okay and I think it's many distributions so wherever here
it's many distributions so wherever here is I expand the joint likelihood alright
我以指数家庭的形式扩展联合可能性吗
is I expand the joint likelihood alright in the form of an exponential family
in the form of an exponential family distribution so these are the sufficient
分布，所以这些是足够的统计信息，它是自然参数
distribution so these are the sufficient statistics it are the natural parameter
statistics it are the natural parameter this organization factor this the
这个组织因素这个功能分数是正确的，所以
this organization factor this the function fraction is d right so so
function fraction is d right so so actually in the new knowledge okay that
实际上，在新知识中，好吧，当我给你时，您可以使用
actually in the new knowledge okay that when I gave you you can use so that this
when I gave you you can use so that this creative innovation will hang on the
创意创新将挂在下一张幻灯片上，实际上我们所做的工作是
creative innovation will hang on the next slide actually Nations we did for
next slide actually Nations we did for the multi body of value alright because
价值的多元体好吧，因为这是一个非常普遍的问题，所以
the multi body of value alright because this is a very general problem okay so
来自指数族的结果，因此您可以与
the results from the exponential family so you talk to the information from
so you talk to the information from there alright so the statistics here
那里好吧，所以这里的统计信息真的很新0 X 0好的，这个博物馆
there alright so the statistics here really become new 0 X 0 ok this museum
really become new 0 X 0 ok this museum becomes your prior and an f of X 0 u 0
成为您的先验，并且f为X 0 u 0好的，这样您就可以阅读主教了
becomes your prior and an f of X 0 u 0 okay so you can read bishops you can
okay so you can read bishops you can look at my notes in the fall formal
看看我在秋天的指数家族的正式资料
look at my notes in the fall formal information of the exponential family
information of the exponential family but basically you can put in this for
但基本上您可以将其用于许多发行版，所以问题是
but basically you can put in this for many distributions right so the question
many distributions right so the question is can you actually divide by a small
你能实际除以一个小的差异近似这个一般
is can you actually divide by a small difference approximations this general
difference approximations this general scenario if we can
如果我们可以看到的情况下，总共大约有50个问题
scenario if we can we have seen about 50 problems all in
we have seen about 50 problems all in one slide and the answer yes you can
一张幻灯片和答案是可以的，所以您必须要做的是放上去
one slide and the answer yes you can so what you have to do to be put on
so what you have to do to be put on everything up because the time is over
一切都结束了，因为时间已经过去了
好吧好吧，您必须使用与之前完全相同的想法
so what you have to do to be put on everything up because the time is over
okay okay you have to use exactly the same ideas as before right
好吧好吧，您必须使用与之前完全相同的想法
same ideas as before right so you capitalize this as Q of Z times Q
所以您将其大写为Z的Q乘Q fitnah，并且您正在寻找
so you capitalize this as Q of Z times Q fitnah and you are looking for kids in
fitnah and you are looking for kids in your people to be the exponential colony
您的人民将成为指数殖民地，并给人们带来惊喜
your people to be the exponential colony and surprise surprise cubes it'll be
and surprise surprise cubes it'll be optimal comes to be exactly exponential
最理想的是成为指数家族，您唯一需要的就是
optimal comes to be exactly exponential family the only thing you need is the
family the only thing you need is the expectation of the parameters and QP
参数和QP的期望值应为指数
expectation of the parameters and QP become so should be the exponential
become so should be the exponential family and you can see the updates are
家庭，您可以看到更新是标准的，唯一需要的是
family and you can see the updates are standard and the only thing you need is
standard and the only thing you need is the expectation with respect to Z of the
关于Z的期望，这里有足够的统计数据影响和
the expectation with respect to Z of the sufficient statistics here affection and
sufficient statistics here affection and Xia okay so basically the problem where
夏好吧，基本上就是这个分布是指数分布的问题
Xia okay so basically the problem where this distribution is the exponential
this distribution is the exponential family conflicting with in this
家庭在某种程度上与这种观察变化相冲突
family conflicting with in this variation of observation in a certain
variation of observation in a certain area in step where you compute this
在步骤中使用ZN的P计算此期望值的区域，然后
area in step where you compute this expectation using P of Z N and then you
expectation using P of Z N and then you plug this same here and you compute this
将其插入此处，您实际上就可以计算出这种变化分布
plug this same here and you compute this variation distribution actually the only
variation distribution actually the only thing you need is you need the
您需要的是您需要β的期望值，因此您可以食用该比率
thing you need is you need the expectation of beta so you eat the rate
expectation of beta so you eat the rate and you can get you know height you can
您可以知道身高，可以得到两个多元变量的结果
and you can get you know height you can get two results for multi variate
get two results for multi variate thousand you can get the result any
千，您可以在任何分布的任何示例中看到结果
thousand you can get the result any distribution any example that we see in
distribution any example that we see in the literature you can use this prognost
您可以使用此预后的文献，它会很好，所以我
the literature you can use this prognost and it will fit in all right so I'm
and it will fit in all right so I'm gonna leave and we're gonna use the
要走了，我们要用星期五快乐的复活节快乐，再见
gonna leave and we're gonna use the enjoy Friday happy Easter and see you on
enjoy Friday happy Easter and see you on Tuesday
周二
我喜欢
enjoy Friday happy Easter and see you on Tuesday
I like it